Are you there?
Da li si tu?
I'm here.
Tu sam.
Help me. My client is going to jail.
Pomozi mi. Moj klijent ide u zatvor.
Oh, no, she's not.
Oh, ne, ne ide.
I think I've got it.
Mislim da sam uspeo.
Really?
Ozbiljno?
Look up Hasson v. Conrad.
Pogledaj Hason protiv Konrada.
Similar circumstantial evidence...
Slicni navodni dokazi...
case was thrown out.
slucaj je odbacen.
Legaleagle, thank you.
,, Ligal-igl", hvala ti.
You are by far the most brilliant mind
Ti imaš daleko najbriljijatniji um...
in this chat room.
u ovoj sobi za cet.
Thank you, Lawyer-girl.
Hvala ti,,, Lojer-girl".
I realize we have certain anonymity here,
Shvatam da ovde postoji odredena anonimnost,
but do you, by any chance, have a name?
ali da li bi mi ti, ako postoji šansa, rekla svoje ime?
It's Charlene.
Šarlin.
I missed you yesterday.
Nedostajala si mi juce.
How was your day?
Kako si ti provela dan?
Uneventful.
Beznacajno.
I exercised for an hour in the morning,
Prvo sam ujutru sat vermena vebala,
poked around in the yard in the afternoon,
popodne se dosadivala u dvorištu,
and visited with a girlfriend down the block in the evening.
I uvece posetila prijateljicu iz komšiluka.
Sounds innocent enough.
Zvuci prilicno nevino.
Don't let my humdrum day fool you, now.
Nemoj da te moj dosadni dan prevari.
I also have a very dark side.
Takode posedujem i svoju vrlo tamnu stranu.
Well, I'm 31
Imam 31 godinu
with long, flowing locks and an athletic body.
dugu kosu i atletsko telo.
Peter, what do you look like?
Piter, kako ti izgledas?
I'm... a little older... 6'2".
Ja sam... malo stariji... 6' 2 ".
My hair is... it's light.
Moja kosa je... svetla.
Uh, it's boyishly light.
Hm, momacki svetla.
And good night to you, Lawyer-girl.
Laku noc tebi,, Lojer-girl".
Gendler.
Gendler.
- Good morning, Mr. Sanderson. - Hi.
- Dobro jutro, gosn. Sanderson. - Zdravo.
Morning, Peter.
Dobro jutro, Piter.
How are you?
Kako si?
Gentlemen.
Gospodo.
Oh, good. Peter's here. We can begin.
O h, dobro. Piter je tu. Mozemo da pocnemo.
Okay. On to pressing business.
U redu. Na neodlone poslove.
Word has come to us
Do nas su došli glasovi
that coffee heiress Mrs. Virginia Arness
da je bogata naslednica gda. Virdinija Arnes
has dismissed her current tax lawyers.
otpustila njene advokate.
Virginia Arness.
Virdinija Arnes.
74 years old, born and raised in Athens, Georgia.
74 godine, rodena i odrasla u Atini, Dordija.
At the age of 13,
U njenoj 13 godini,
she was shipped off to boarding school in England,
...poslata je u internat u Englesku,
where she's been residing until just recently.
...gde je boravila sve do skoro.
That was only two days ago.
To je bilo samo do pre dva dana.
Impressive.
Impresivno.
Now, we've all heard
Svi smo culi...
that Mrs. Arness has a penchant for thriftiness.
da gospodjica Arneshas ima apetit za napredovanje.
And that she brings new meaning to the term "conservative."
I donela je novi znacaj terminu "Ocuvanje"
It's not going to be easy.
Nece biti lako...
She's paranoid and suspicious. Peter...
Ona je paranoicna i sumnjicava. - Peter...
I'm her guy.
Ja sam momak za nju.
I'm single. I'll give her nights, weekends.
Sam sam. Mogu da joj pruzim noci, vikende.
Aren't you getting married on Sunday, Todd?
Zar se ti nezenis u subotu, Todd?
That's flexible.
To je fleksibilno.
And, Peter, I wouldn't want this to interfere
I Peter, ne zelim da se mesam u
with your family's Hawaiian vacation.
tvoj familijarni Havajski odmor.
You go on.
Vi nastavite.
I got it all taken care of.
Ja cu se pobrinuti za to.
Mahalo.
M a h a i o.
Well, that's very admirable of you, Todd.
Pa to je divno od tebe, Todd.
I mean, your youth definitely makes you an ass...
Mislio sam, vi mladi definitivno cepite svoje dup...
...et to the company,
...e u kompaniji,
especially at the annual softball game.
narocito na godisnjoj igri softball-a.
But to an archconservative, 74-year-old woman?
Ali jednoj konzervativnoj 74-godisnjoj zeni?
What will we do is not charge Mrs. Arness one single red cent
Ono sto cemo uraditi, je da necemo optuziti gospodju Arneson ni za jedan crveni cent
for her estate planning.
za njeno planiranje.
Why?
ZASTO?
Because we don't care about that measly fee.
Zato sto nam nije stalo za taj bolesni ulog.
We use it as a loss leader to get her corporate business,
Upotrebicemo ga kao stetnog lidera zajednicki akcionarski posao,
the multibillion-dollar Arness coffee conglomerate.
multi milijarderskoj arness kafa konglomerata.
Hmm.
H m m.
How may I help you, Howie?
Kako ti mogu pomoci, Howie?
Just thought I'd congratulate you on turning it around.
Upravo ti cestitam na uvrtanju.
Turning what around?
Uvrtanju?
You snaked Gendler.
Zeznuo si Gendier-a.
Please. Gendler doesn't bother me.
Molim te. Gendier mi uopste nesmeta.
Oh, that's right. He doesn't bother you.
O, pa to je tacno. On ti nesmeta.
What the heck was I thinking?
Ne znam zasto sam to i pomislio?
Listen, I thought maybe after work
Slusaj, mozda posle posla.
you and me go tie one on,
Ti i ja,
maybe check out some of the local talent.
mozda proverimo neke lokalne talente.
Can't. I'm meeting Mrs. Arness at 6:00.
Nemogu, imam sastanak sa gospodjom Arnessat u 18:00.
And by the way, it's "You and I go tie one on,"
I uzgred ti i ja da idemo...
not "You and me go."
Ne idemo mi.
Somebody messaging you here.
Neko ti je upravo poslao poruku.
Who's Lawyer-girl?
Ko je ta advokatica?
Nobody.
Niko.
Whoa. Did someone make a blind Internet date?
Opa. Da li je neko ugovorio slepi sudar na internetu?
No. I mean, you know, well, technically, but no.
Ne. Mislim, ti znas, ovaj tehnicki ali ne.
I met her in a legal chat room.
Upoznao sam je na legalnom chat-u
She's, uh, very classy and smart.
U, prava je klasa a i pametna je.
When do you nail her?
Kada si je nagovorio?
I'm courting her tonight at 7:00.
Pozvao sam je veceras u 19:00.
Oh, jeez. You're courting her. Sounds like a hot one.
O, Isuse. Pozvao si je kuci. Izgleda da je bas zestoka.
And this is her?
Ovo je ona?
Yeah, she's attractive, isn't she?
Pa da, bas je atraktivna, zar ne?
I suppose. It's not my cup of tea.
Pretpostavljam. Nije moj tip.
What do you... she is universally cute.
Sta ti je... Bas je slatka.
Eh, she's a little too anemic-Iooking, Petey.
E, ona je atletomanicno zgodna.
I like my jello to jiggle, if I'm not being too subtle.
Ja nisam zigolo, jednostavno nisam njen nivo.
You're not being too subtle.
Nisi njen nivo.
All right, as long as she spins your knobs, I'm happy for you.
Uredu je, dokle god te vrte u cvor, ja se nebrinem za tebe.
Have you nailed anyone since Kate?
Jesi li vec neku otkad Kate?
Nail... I was supposed to call her.
Neku... ja sam mislio da je pozovem.
Sofia, can you get my wife on the phone?
Sofia, mozes li mi dati zenu na telefon?
- Ex-wife. - Ex-wife on the phone?
- Bivsu-zenu. - Bivsu-zenu na telefon?
Right away.
Odmah.
Can't help you with this one, pal. See you later.
Nemogu ti pomoci oko ovog, brate. Vidimo se kasnije.
Peter, you cannot break another promise to these kids.
Peter, nemozes prekrsiti jos jedno obecanje deci.
You just can't.
Jednostavno nemozes.
I said I couldn't take them to Hawaii.
Rekao sam da nemogu da ih vodim na Havaje.
I didn't say I couldn't take them.
Nisam rekao da nemogu da ih pokupim.
They can spend the week with me.
Mogu da provedu vikend samnom
They are gonna be so disappointed.
Bice mnogo razocarani.
I can't talk to you right now.
Ne mogu da pricam vise.
Um... Daddy can't take you to Hawaii.
Tata nemoze da vas vodi na Havaje.
Oh, darn.
O, prokletstvo.
He always does this.
On uvek to radi.
Sanderson, party of two.
Sanderson, dva mesta.
Oh, you're the last to arrive.
O, vi ste poslednji stigli.
How long has she been here?
Koliko je vec ovde?
Mmm, about 20 minutes.
M m m, oko 20 minuta.
Was she trouble?
Da li je nervozna?
Thank you.
Hvala vam.
Hello. I'm Peter Sanderson.
Zdravo. Ja sam Peter Sanderson.
Well, I'm glad they didn't send a child.
Dobro, drago mi je sto nisu poslali dete.
I told them I specifically wanted someone my own age.
Rekla sam im stritno da zelim nekog mojih godina.
What a wonderful French bulldog.
Kakav divan francuski buldog.
My mother had one. They make great companions.
Moja majka ima jednog. Oni su pravo drustvo.
What's her name?
- Kako joj je ime?
His name is William Shakespeare.
Njegovo ime je wiiiiam shakespere.
Well, of course.
Pa da, naravno.
Now, I've heard about your unfortunate escapade.
Ovaj, cuo sam o vasem nesrecnom povecavanju
I don't have escapades.
Ja nemam povecanje.
Fiasco with your previous attorney.
Fiasko sa vasim bivsim zastupnikom.
The man was a thieving criminal.
Taj covek je bio lopov i criminalac.
Just because I have a lot of money
Zbog toga sto ja imam puno novca
doesn't give people the right to overcharge.
ne daje ljudima za pravo natovare preko.
I do not enjoy being taken advantage of.
Ne uzivam kada mi se oduzme prednost.
Which is why our service is free of charge.
Pitate se zasto su nase usluge besplatne.
After all, you worked hard for your money.
Posle svega, vi ste tesko zaradili taj novac.
I'm an heiress.
Ja sam naslednica.
An heiress who worked hard to keep her money.
Naslednica, koja se mucila da sacuva novac.
Now, shall we get down to business?
Dakle, hocemo li sada da predjemo na posao?
Fine.
Divno.
So, now you may hand over your proposal.
Tako, sada vi mozete da iznesete vasu ponudu.
I'll take it with me.
Ponecu je sa sobom.
Proposal?
Ponudu?
Well, I was expecting to meet with you tomorrow.
Ovaj, ja sam ocekivao da se sastanem sa vama sutra.
I was assured the proposal would be ready
Ja sam bila sigurna da je ponuda bila spremna
for this afternoon.
danas popodne.
I see no point in our meeting tomorrow.
Ne vidim svrhu naseg sastanka sutra.
Excuse me. Madam, I'm sorry.
Izvinjavam se. Madam, zao mi je.
We have a no-dog policy in the lounge.
Politika ove kuce zabranjuje uvodjenje zivotinja.
Unfortunately, I'm gonna have to ask you to remove the dog.
Nazalost, ja moram da vas zamolim da izvedete psa.
Excuse me. I am Mrs. Arness' attorney,
Izvinite. Ja sam zastupnik gospodje Arness,
and because there is no sign posted regarding dogs,
i posto nigde ne stoji nista u vezi pasa,
that means there is no policy toward dogs.
Sto znaci da nema nikakve polise koja se odnosi na pse.
Now, if you want to avoid a legal situation,
Dakle, ako hocete da izbegnete nelegalnu situaciju,
I would suggest you run to the kitchen
ja bih vam predlozio da otrcite pravo u kuhinju
and get some tuna tartare for William Shakespeare
i donesete tuna-tartare za wiiiiam-a shakespeare-a
on the house.
na racun kuce.
Yes, sir.
Da gospodine.
I'm terribly sorry, ma'am.
Veoma mi je zao gospodjo.
Where and when tomorrow?
Gde i kada sutra?
Hello, Mr. Sanderson.
Zdravo, g. Sanderson.
Oh, Mrs. Kline. Always a pleasure.
Oh, gospodjo Kiine. Zadovostvo mi je, takodje.
And when am I going to get to babysit
I kada da nabavim baby-siterku
with your charming little Georgey again?
sa vasim malim George-om ponovo?
Oh, uh, well, uh, soon,
O, u, pa, uskoro,
because he just loves coming over to your place.
zato sto on prosto voli da dolazi kod vas.
Uh, Mr. Sanderson?
U, g. Sanderson?
Those Latin people who were skulking around...
Ti latino ljudi koji zabusavaju okolo...
Oh. They were looking at the Aruda house.
oh. Oni su gledali ruda kucu.
Casing it?
Renoviraju?
No, uh, to buy it.
N e, da je kupe.
Oh, please.
O, molim vas.
If they're in this block and not carrying a leaf blower...
Ako su oni u ovom bloku a nije ima stalo da...
Yeah.
Da.
Well, I'd love to discuss this with you further,
Dobro, voleo bih da razgovaram sa vama i dalje,
but I'm expecting someone.
ali ocekujem nekog.
Ohh.
Oo.
Yeah.
Da.
Hey.
Hej.
Hi.
Pozdrav.
Yeah.
Da.
I hope you like cham...
Nadam se da volis sampanj...
...poo.
...njac.
What's up, baby?
Sta je bilo duso?
Ooh, champagne. I love champagne.
Ou, sampanjac, mnogo volim sampanjac.
This for me?
Ovo je za mene?
Oh, I'm sorry. I think you have the wrong house.
O, zao mi je. Mislim da ste pogresili kucu.
It is damn good to finally connect.
Prokleto je dobro sto smo se konacno spojili.
Pardon me?
Oprostite?
It's me, fool... Charlene.
Ja sam bre, budalo... Charlene.
Ooh, food.
Ooo, hrana.
What?
Sta?
It's me, honey. Your date... Lawyer-girl.
Ja sam, seceru. Tvoj sastanak... advokatica.
You can't be.
Ne mozes biti.
Hey, hey, hey. Leave that alone.
Hej, hej, hej. Ostavi to.
Well, why can't I?
Pa, zasto nemogu?
Because you're not a blonde.
Zato sti ti nisi plavusa.
Can't get nothing past you.
Nemoze ti nista proci.
You must be a bomb-ass lawyer.
Ti mora da razbijac od advokata.
Oh, look at all of these pretty candles...
Oo, pogledaj sve te prelepe svece...
all romantic and shit.
sve romanticno i usrano.
Somebody was planning on getting some booty tonight.
Neko je planirao da privede nekog veceras.
Hey! Leave that alone. There are settings.
Hej! Ostavi to. Ja sam to sredjivao.
And you can't be Charlene, because Charlene is more of...
I ti nemozes biti Charlene, zato sto je ona vise...
Skinny white broad?
belja po telu?
Yeah.
Daa.
You know, I get that a lot.
Znas, ja imam toga puno.
But that's your fault you're thinking that, bro.
ALi tu si u krivu razmisli o tome, brale.
You must have not have took a good look at that picture.
TI mora da nisi dobro pogledao fotografiju.
I have looked at that picture a lot,
Gledao sam tu sliku mnogo,
and trust me, you are not in it.
i veruj me, ti nisi na njoj.
Mm-hmm.
Mm - hmm.
Move, move, move. Let me do it.
Bezi, bezi, bezi... Pusti mene.
See?
Vidis?
There I am.
Evo me.
Sorry you got it twisted, dog.
Izvini sto si dobio malo uvrnutu, keru.
I don't get a lot of photo ops where I been.
Ne posedujem mnogo svojih slika.
Where exactly have you been?
Gde si ti uistinu bila?
I got a rumble in the jungle. We still having dinner or what?
Lmala sam tucu u dzungli. Imamo li jos uvek veceru ili sta?
I asked you a question.
Pitao sam te nesto.
Rolex.
Roiex.
Rolex?
Roiex?
I did time, baby, but I ain't do the crime.
Lmala sam vremena, srce, ali nisam pocinila zlocin.
You're a convict?
Ti si optuzena?
Bump that.
Ma pali...
Shoot, Roscoe cracked that door.
Ovako, Roscoe je slomio ta vrata
I kicked it off the heezy and bounced.
I sutnuli su me lagano i napustili.
For real, though.
Za stvarno, mada.
What did you just say?
Sta si mi ti ustvari pricala.
What, don't you hear good?
Sta, zar necujes dobro?
All right.
Uredu.
Let's see. How can I put this?
Da vidimo. Kako da...?
I was recently liberated from a correctional facility...
Ja sam nedavno bila oslobodjena od ispravnih olaksica...
All right. I get it.
uredu je. Shatio sam.
You're in the big house, and you get someone to type for you,
Ti si u velikoj kuci, i nasla si nekoga ko ce da kuca za tebe,
and you get on the Internet, and you misrepresent yourself.
i dospela si na internet i predstavila se umesto tebe.
It happens, and I'm a sucker,
To se desava, a ja sam glupan,
but now you have to go, because this is over.
ali sada ti moras da ides, zato sto je sada gotovo.
Unh-unh. No, no, no.
U - u. Ne, ne, ne.
Biscuit, you misrepresented yourself.
Kolacicu, zaboravio si da ti predstavljas sebe.
Boyishly light... please.
Svetao momak... molim te.
Gray.
Seeed.
You said you was a criminal lawyer.
Rekao si da si advokat za kriminal.
I pulled your file.
Provalila sam te.
You're just some sorry-ass tax attorney.
A ti si sam niki glupavi zastupnik.
A tax lawyer is a criminal lawyer.
Finansijski zastupnik je i advokat za kriminal.
Oh, yeah?
Ooo, kako da ne?
Well, good, 'cause that's why I'm here.
Pa onda, dobro, zbog toga sam i ovde.
Well, do tell.
Pa, onda reci.
Well, I want to reopen my case.
Evo, zelim da mi ponovo otvoris slucaj.
And what did you do, smoke some homies on a drive-by?
I sta si ti uradila, popusila si nekom u kolima?
Smoke? Homies?
Popusila?
Well, you a regular gangster, huh?
Pa, ti si pravi gangster, huu?
No, man. I was in for armed robbery, but I didn't do it.
Ne, covece. Bila sam u oruzanoj pljacki, ali nisam to uradila.
Yeah, nobody did it.
Da, niko to nije uradio.
I can't be having this conversation
Nemogu da se ponasam u ovom ragovoru
because you're a criminal-type.
zato sto si ti tip krimanalca.
If I was a criminal, I would have shanked you
Da sam kriminalac, da li bih se drzala tebe.
when I had that knife in my hand.
Kada imam taj noz u ruci.
The fact that you even said that is a problem for me.
Cinjenica je da podjednak problem za mene.
- But I didn't think that. - It's just time to go.
- Ali nisam razmisljao tako. - Vreme je da krenes.
Please, just listen to me. Just give me one second.
Molim te, saslusaj me. Samo mi daj sekundu.
No, I don't have a second.
Ne, nemam vremena.
Okay, can I just say something, please?
Uredu, mogu li samo da kazem nesto, molim te?
What?
Sta?
I didn't do the crime.
Nisam kriva.
You rude mother...
Ti majka...
I ain't goin'.
Ja nisam...
It's your baby, Peter, and don't you deny it!
To je tvoje dete Peter, i nemoj to da porices!
That DNA test told on you!
Ne porici to!
You lie, Peter!
Ti lazes, Peter!
You know lil' Kareem is yours!
Ti znas da mi je stalo!
Why?!
ZASTO?!
How you gonna do me like that, Peter?!
Kako si mogao to da mi uradis, Peter?!
You told me I was your beautiful African Queen.
Rekao si mi da sam tvoja prelepa africka kraljica.
And I loved you for that, Peter!
I ja sam te volela zbog toga, Peter!
I didn't care if your little thing was curved.
Nisam marila, sto je tvoja mala stvar malo kriva.
And lil' Kareem don't want your child support.
Nisam zelela tvoju pomoc za dete.
He just want a relationship with his white daddy.
On je samo hteo vezu sa svojim belim ocem.
A little chocolate/vanilla swirl
Mali cokoladni - vanilasti.
from that magical night at the crackhouse.
Od te magicne noci u oronuloj kuci.
Oh!
O h!
Come on. Just be quiet!
Hajde bre. Samo budi tiha!
Wait just a second. My shoes.
Sacekaj sekundu, moje cipele.
- Mr. Sanderson? - Whoa!
- G. Sanderson? - Voa!
Is everything okay?
Da li je sve uredu?
I thought I heard Negro.
Mislim da sam cula neke crnce.
No. No Negro spoken here.
Ne. Ja nisam cuo nijednog crnca.
Oh.
Ouu.
Well... good night, then.
Pa... laku noc, onda.
Oh, uh...
Ou, uu...
good night.
laku noc.
Come on!
Hajde!
Come on, come on!
Hajde, hajde!
You stay. You stay. You wait right there.
Stani, stani. Cekaj me ovde.
Who you callin'?
Koga zoves?
The police.
Policiju.
Police department. Sergeant Panella. Please hold.
Poiicijska stanica. Porucnik Paneiia. Molim vas sacekajte.
What's that?
Sta je to?
It's all of our e-mails.
To su svi nasi email-ovi.
would be interested in hearing
Mislim da bi bili zainteresovani da cuju o ovome
about you looking for Boom-boom in the federal pen?
o onome sto ti trazis bum-bum
And I'll send a photo.
I ja cu poslati slike.
Thanks for holding. Can I help you?
Hvala sto ste sacekali. Mogu li vam pomoci?
Now, this is just for tonight, understand?
Ovako, ovo je samo za veceras, razumes?
A'ight.
Uredu.
I can work with this.
Snaci cu se sa ovim.
But, uh, look, don't be gettin' no ideas
Ali, vidi, nemoj ni da pomisljas
about sneakin' up in here and hittin' this ass,
da se usunjas ovde i pogodis me u guzu,
'cause you blew your chance with this fine sister.
jer si upropastio svaku sansu sa ovakvom sekom.
Dare to dream.
Sanjaj o tome.
Tsk. Please.
Molim te.
Oh, my God! A bed!
Ooo, moj boze! Krevet!
Oh, a nice, big, cushy bed.
Ooo, fini, veliki, krevet sa jastucima.
Ohh, no roommates, no cellmates.
Ooo, bez cimera, sama samcata.
Charlene?
Charlene?
Charlene.
Charlene.
Charlene! Come on, you're not fooling anybody.
Charlene! Hajde, nemoj da zezas.
Who that? Who there?
Ko je to? Ko je to?
Who want it with Lene?
Ko hoce sa Lene-om
I put some bagels outside.
Ostavio sam neke torbe napolju.
I thought we could discuss your case.
Mislio sa da mozemo da razgovaramo o tvom slucaju.
Ahh!
Aaa!
What up, dog? Where 'em bagels at?
Sta je, keru? Gde sam stavila torbe?
Hey, guess what, girlfriend? Your game is up.
Hej, pogodi sta, devojko? Tvojoj igri je dosao kraj.
Because I burned all those e-mails,
Zato sto sam spalio sve te email-ove.
including the second set hidden in the lining of your coat.
Ukljucujuci i rezervnu kopiju iz tvog kaputa.
And I deleted everything off my computer.
I izbrisao sam sve iz mog racunara.
So I never met you, and you never met me.
Tako da se ti i ja nikada nismo ni upoznali.
Don't even try, girlfriend, because it's locked.
Nemoj ni da pokusavas, devojko, zato sto je zakljucano.
And now I am going to go get my kids,
I sada ja odoh da pokupim svoju decu,
as in innocent young persons
koje kao nevina mlade osobe
who will never even know you were here.
nikada nece znati da si bila ovde.
So now just go.
Tako da sada ides.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Idi, idi, idi, idi, idi, idi!
And locky locky!
I zakljuc, zakljuc!
So ta-ta.
Ta t a-t a.
And watch out. The gate closes automatically.
I pazi kapija se zakljucava automatski.
Well, what about my stuff?
Ali, sta je sa mojim stvarima?
Oh, it's right there on the street.
Oo, evo su ovde na ulici.
You put my stuff on the trash?
Bacio si moje stvari u djubre?
Oh. Well, you know what?
Oou. Znas sta?
I wish you well. I really do.
Zelim ti sve najbolje. Stvarno zelim.
And you know what? I had a great, great time.
I znas sta? Proveo sam, veoma dobro.
It was really fun.
Bilo je stvarno zabavno.
So, oh, well.
Dakle, ou, dobro.
I guess I'll just see you in my next life.
Predpostavljam da cu te videti u mom sledecem zivotu.
Heh heh heh heh. Bye!
Ha ha ha ha. Zbogom!
Ha ha. I'll see you when you get home.
Ha ha. Videcu te kada dodjes kuci.
So I said to him,
Dakle rekla sam mu,
"Just 'cause you whisked me to Paris on your private jet
"samo zato sto si me pozvao u Pariz u tvom privatnom avionu
doesn't mean I'm gonna sleep with you."
neznaci da cu spavati s'tobom."
What does he think I am? A hooker?
Sta on misli da sam ja, kurva?
Can Aunt Ashley edit herself, please?
Moze li da on zadovolji sebe, molim te?
You stayed in the same room with him.
Ti ostajes Edin u istoj sobi sa njim.
What did you expect?
Pa sta si ocekivala?
Hello. It was a suite... plenty of floor space.
Halo. Bilo je svita... puno prostora u sobi na patosu.
Sweetiepie, have a wonderful time. I love you.
Slatkisu, provedi prijatno vreme. Volim te.
Please be good to your brother and help him with his reading.
Molim te budi dobra prema svom bratu i pomozi mu oko njegovog citanja.
- I will. - Thank you.
- Hocu. - Hvala ti.
Is he still having problems?
Da li on jos uvek ima probleme?
Oh, he struggles every day, but he's improving.
Ou, ma bori se stim svakog dana, ali improvizuje nesto.
Dad's here.
Otac je stigao.
Thank you, sweetiepie.
Hvala ti, slatkisu.
Don't worry, sweetie.
Nebrini, slatkisu.
Daddy's stupid, too, and he became a lawyer.
Tata je glup isto, i postace advokat.
Ashley!
Ashiey!
I'm not stupid.
Ja nisam glup.
- That's right. - No, no, no. Of course not.
- To je tacno. - Ne, ne, ne. Naravno da ne.
Hey, Dad's here.
Hej, tata je stigao.
Speak of the dummy.
Mi o glupanu, a evo ga.
Hey, how's my little girl doin', huh?
Hej, kako je moja mala devojcica?
Hi, Dad.
Zdravo, tata.
Hey, how's it goin', big guy?
Hej, kako ide momcino?
Ahhh, here you go.
Ahhh, evo ga.
Hi, Kate.
Zdravo, Kate.
Hi.
Zdravo.
Oh, Ashley, I didn't realize you were gonna be here.
Oou, Ashley, nisam znao da ces i ti biti ovde.
What a pleasant surprise.
Kakvo prijatno iznenadjenje.
Peter, you're almost aging well.
Peter, ti bas staris dobro.
Okay, I thought we'd go down to the club and take a swim.
Ovako, evo kako cemo. Idemo dole do kluba na plivanje.
Ooh, that sounds much more fun than Maui.
Oou, to zvuci mnogo bolje od mauli.
You know, Ashley, not all of us earn our living
Znas sta, Ashley, nismo svi zaslusili u nasem zivotu
by milking rich geriatrics out of their money.
da hranimo bogate gerijatre za njihov novac.
Some of us have to work for a living.
Neko od nas mora da radi za zivot.
You sound much more intelligent with your mouth shut.
Peter, izgledas mnogo inteligentnije kada cutis.
Let's not start this. I don't have time.
Nemojte opet. Nemam vremena.
Kids, go get your stuff.
Deco, idite po svoje stvari.
All right, fine.
Uredu, dobro.
But I warned you
Ali upozorila sam te
about marrying the first jerk-off you met out of college.
u vezi udaje za prvog kretena koga sretnes posle koledza.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a date.
Sada, me izvinite, lmam sudar.
Don't be good.
Nemoj biti dobra.
What morgue did you find this one at?
Kog si mrtvaca sada nasla da hranis?
Stop being so childish.
Prestani da budes detinjast.
Hey.
Hej.
Wow. You look beautiful.
Wow. Izgledas predivno.
Thank you.
Hvala.
Mmm.
Mmm.
Uh, hi.
Uf, zdravoi.
Uh, Peter, this is Glen.
Uf, Peter, ovo je Glen.
Hey.
Hej.
Hey, Mr. Sanderson. Nice to see you.
Hej, g. Sanderson. Drago mi je sto vas vidim.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
Da da, i meni je drago.
Uh, what do you say we get this road on the show?
Uf, sta kazes da ovaj put napravimo sou?
Okay.
Vazi.
I will meet you outside.
Vidimo se napolju.
Road on the show.
"Napravimo sou".
Just don't.
Samo nemoj.
How old is he?
Koliko ima godina?
Younger.
Mladji je.
- What does he do? - Golf instructor.
- Cime se bavi? - Instruktor golfa.
- How do you know that? - What?
- Kako to znas? - Sta?
Well, you think you know somebody,
Dobro, mislis da znas nekog,
and then one day you wake up in Thailand missing a kidney.
i onda jednog dana probudis se na Tajlandu bez bubrega.
He could have made up this whole golf identity.
Mozda je izmislio ceo identitet intruktora golfa.
He caddied for you when he was 14.
Sluzio te je kada je imao 14 god.
That's little Glenny?
To je mali Glenny?
Does that bother you?
Da li ti to smeta?
Not at all.
Ne, uopste.
Go have fun on your statutory weekend.
Idi i provedi se na svoj zakoniti vikend.
This does too bother you. I know you.
Ovo ti smeta. Znam te.
Do you want to talk about it?
Hoces li da pricamo o tome?
Well, it just looks a little silly.
Pa, to lici samo na malog glupog...
Hang on.
Sacekaj.
Hello?
Halo?
Some things never change.
Nesto se nikada nemanja.
I can't talk right now.
Ne mogu sada da pricam.
Well, put him on.
Dobro, daj mi ga.
Hi.
Zdravo.
You promised us you'd take us snorkeling.
Obeca si da ces da nas vodis.
Things come up. That's life.
Nesto je iskrslo. Takav ti je zivot.
I know. I'm really, really sorry.
Znam. Stvarno mi je jako zao.
But now it's over. It's new. We're gonna have a lot of fun.
Ali sada je gotovo. Novo. Lepo cemo se zabaviti.
Now, what's new? What's new with you?
Sada, sta ima novo? Sta ima novo kod tebe?
Well, I got the female lead in the school play "Oklahoma!"
Pa, postala sam lidersica, u skolskom "Oklahoma!"
Hey, that's great. Congratulations.
Hej, pa to je divno. Cestitam.
And how 'bout you, big guy? How's school?
I sta ima kod tebe momce? Kako skola?
I don't like school.
Nevolim skolu
Well, nobody likes school,
Dobro, niko nevoli skolu,
but there must be something you like about it.
ali mora da ima nesto sto ti se svidja.
He got into a fight the other day.
Potukao se pre neki dan.
Why? Why'd you get in a fight?
Zasto? Zasto si se tukao?
Some kids called me a baby 'cause of the way I read.
Neka deca su me nazvala beba, zato sto tako citam.
Some of the greatest minds of all time had trouble learning,
Neki od velikih umova imali su uvek problema sa ucenjem,
like Edgar Allan Poe and Albert Einstein
kao npr. Edgar A. Poe, pa Albert Einstein
and, uh, Ozzy Osbourne.
i, uf, Ozzy Osbourne.
Ozzy rules.
Ha, ha. Ozzy rula.
Ozzy rules. Okay.
Ozzy rula. Uredu.
Dad, what's goin' on?
Oce, sta se desava?
You two wait here. I'll be right back.
Vas dvoje sacekajte ovde. Sad cu ja.
Hey!
Hej!
Whoa, whoa. Where you think you're goin', milk?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Gde si ti krenuo mlecni?
This here's a charitable event.
Ovo ovde je za dobrotvorne svrhe.
You wants to get in, you gots to make a donation.
Ako hoces da udjes, moras da das neku donaciju.
Trust me, it is off the hook in there.
Veruj mi, prepuno je kukica unutra.
Off the what? I live here.
Prepuno cega? Ja zivim ovde bre?
I don't care if you're Halle Berry, man.
Ne interesuje me ni da si Halie Berry, covece.
No donation, no entry.
Nema donacije, nema ulaza.
How 'bout if I call the police?
Kako bi bilo da ja pozovem policiju?
Have a nice time.
Lepo se provedite.
Oh, yeah.
Ou, da.
Yeah, baby, show me.
Da, baby, pokazi mi.
Hey! What the hell is going on here?
Hej! Sta se bre dogadja ovde?
Oh, yo, P., it's cool.
Ou, jo, pi., samo opusteno.
See, I hit up my homegirl
Vidis, ovo je moja ortakinja
'cause I had to get my hair done, as we both know.
koja mi namesta kosu, dobro, kao sto oboje znamo.
And then she called a friend. They holler to other friends.
I onda je ona pozvala prijatelje. Pa su onda oni pozvali svoje i eto.
Before you know it, we got us a house par-ty.
Pre nego sto si znao, mi smo nam napravili zurkicu.
I want everyone out of here now!
Hocu da svi sada izadju napolje!
People!
Ljudi!
Loosen your panties, Grandma.
Lzgubila si svoje gacice, bako.
Look, you lock me out, no money, no place to go.
Gledaj, zakljucao si me napolju, bez para, nemam gde da odem.
I mean, a girl got to get her cheese on.
Mislim, devojka je dobila sto je htela.
Seven.
Sedan.
This is insane!
Ovo je ludo!
My boss' sister lives across the street.
Sestra mog sefa zivi preko puta ulice.
I can't have all these peop...
Nemogu da imam sve ove ljude...
Hey!
Hej!
Give me a hard seven, baby.
Daj mi tesku sedmicu, baby.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hej, hej, hej, hej.
She doesn't even have her driver's permit.
Ona nema jos ni dopustenje da vozi.
Dad.
Oce.
Do not go...
Ne idi...
Roll! Uh!
Roii! Uf!
Come on.
Hajde.
Don't inhale.
Nemoj udisati.
All right, now. Go on and toss them bones, lil' man.
Uredu je, sad. Daj mi bonus, covece.
Hey! Give me...
Hej! Daj mi...
I'm on a roll, Dad.
Ja sam na redu, oce.
Get out.
- Izadji.
I want you and your dogs to go back to the pound now.
Hocu da se ti i tvoji psi vratite nazad odakle ste dosli.
What?
Sta?
Well, it was the dogs?
Dobro, bilo je pasa?
Because she said dogs, and then I said dogs,
Zato sto je ona rekla psi, pa sam ja zato rekao psi,
so I assumed that would be okay.
tako da mislim da je to uredu.
Huh?
Haa?
Whoo!
Whoooo!
Bye, Tamika. Y'all be good, now.
Zbogom, Tamika. Bicu dobro, sad.
Bye.
Zbogom.
Hey, hey. Y'all got to go.
Hej, hej. Morate da idete.
- A'ight. - That's a'ight.
- Uredu. - Uredu je.
Hey, baby, gonna go.
Hey, baby, idem ja.
Oh, bye, Bear. Thank you so much.
Ou, zbogom, medo. Hvala ti mnogo.
Party's over. Okay. Thanks for coming.
Zurka je gotova. Uredu. Hvala sto ste bili.
But that's it. It's over.
Ali to je gotovo.
You know he wants to know that.
Znas on hoce da zna to.
I don't know about that. I'll see you.
Neznam za to. Videcu.
- Okay. Bye, baby. - Bye-bye.
- Uredu. Zdravo, baby. - zdravo- zdravo.
Hey.
Hej.
- How you doin', neighbor? - What's up?
- Kako ste komsinice? - Sta ima?
What are you still doing here?
Sta ti jos radis ovde?
- What was all that, Dad? - Dad, who's this?
O cemu se uopste radi, oce? - Oce, ko je ovo?
This is no one.
To je niko.
Tsk! What's up, lil' Romeo?
Sta ima mali romeo?
My name is Charlene. What's your name?
Moje ime je Charlene. A kako se ti zoves?
I'm Georgey.
Ja sam Georgey.
You cannot meet a nonexistent person.
Nemozes da se upoznajes sa nepostojecom osobom.
Can Charlene come to the club?
Moze li Charlene s'nam u klub?
Club? What club?
Klub? Koji bre klub?
We're not going to a club, remember?
Mi neidemo u klub, zar se nesecas?
We're going to Hawaii,
Mi idemo na Havaje, zar se nesecas?
Okay, you know the routine. Outski!
Uredu, znas rutinu. Napolje.
- Out! Let's go. - Come on, man!
- Napoljet! Hajde. - Ma daj bre, covece!
Sarah, get the door. Come on. Out.
Sarah, vrata. Hajde, napolje.
Out, out, out!
Napolje, Napolje, Napolje!
- Wait! - What?
- Cekaj! - Sta?
Give me my money, lil' boy.
Daj moj novac, momce.
That money should go to charity!
Taj novac treba da ide u dobrotvorne svrhe!
Ohh!
Ooo!
What did...
Sta je...
Hey, I live here.
Hej, ja zivim ovde.
Yeah!
Da!
What?
Sta?
Okay, you guys.
Ovako, momci.
You know, you order hot dogs, and you splash and frolic
Znate, narucite hot-dogs, prskanje i igranje...
and just put everything on my account and just have fun.
stavite sve na moj racun i lepo se zabavljajte.
Didn't you bring your bathing suit?
Nisi poneo svoje kupace?
Oh, no. I'm having tea with a client.
O, ne. Ja pijem caj sa svojim klijentom.
But I will be right back.
Ali cu se uskoro vratiti.
Whatever you say.
Kako ti kazes.
Want to go swimming?
Idemo na plivanje?
With you?
Sa tobom?
Forget you.
Zaboravi.
Ow!
Au!
How's it looking?
Kako izgleda?
Well, I was up all night proofing.
Dobro, celu noc sam ispitivao.
It's absolutely brilliant.
Absolutno brilijantno.
And you've got the cleanest background check I've ever seen.
I imas najcistiju biografiju ikad vidjenu.
That background check cost me a lot of fun in my life.
Ta biografija me je kostala mnogo zezanja u mom zivotu.
What's crackin', ma?
Sta ima majko?
I'm lookin' for the Sanderson table.
Trazim sto g. Sandersona.
We old college buddies.
Mi smo stare kolege sa koledza.
O-O-Okay. He's i-in the dining room.
U-u-uredu. On je u trpezariji.
I-I'll show you.
Pokazacu vam...
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Ooo, ne, ne, ne, ne, ne.
I tell you what... I'll surprise him.
Ma hocu da ga iznenadim.
No, you're in great shape. I'm gonna take off.
Ne, ti si u velikoj formi
All right, you're right. Nothing could go wrong.
Uredu, upravu si nista nemoze poci naopako.
I've done this a million times with important clients,
Radio sam vec ovo milion puta sa veoma vaznim licnostima.
so I'm fine.
Tako, da sam dobro...
- Shazam. - What?
- Sazam. - Sta?
Oh, no.
Oo, ne.
Oh, swing it, you cocoa goddess.
Oo, ljuljaj, boginjo kokosa.
Cocoa Goddess? That's the rude shock I was telling you about.
Boginjo kokosa? To je taj ruzni shok koji sam hteo da ti ispricam.
That's Charlene?
To je Charlene?
Did she see me?
Da li me je videla?
Okay, okay, okay, police.
Uredu, uredu, uredu, poiicija.
Uh, no. Won't get here fast enough.
Uuu, ne. Nece doci tako brzo.
Uh, security.
Uuu, obezbedjenje.
No, she could probably take him.
Ne, slomila bi ga.
Uh, money.
Uu, novac.
She'll take money.
Uzece novac.
Hi, hi. Here, just... Here's whatever.
Zdravo, zdravo. Evo, samo... evo sta god.
And there's more where that came from if you just leave now.
I bice jos, samo nas napusti sad.
No. Unh-unh, boyfriend. We got business.
Ne. Unn - unn, decko. Mi imamo posao.
Boyfriend?
Decko?
Oh, didn't I tell you? We're dating now.
Ou, nisam ti rekao? Mi se vidjamo sada.
It's some kind of street talk.
To je neka vrsta ulicnog razgovora.
It's street for "I'm not going nowhere
To je ulicni za "ja neidem nigde
until you help my problem go away."
dok mi ne pomognes da resim svoj problem."
Look, Mrs. Arness, a very important client,
Vidi, gdja Arness, nam je veoma vazan klijent,
is due here any minute.
i samo sto nije dosla.
Good afternoon.
Dobar dan.
Mr. Sanderson?
Dobar dan. G. Sanderson?
Oh, yes. He's in the dining room.
Oo, da. On je u trpezariji.
Thank you.
Hvala vam.
Charlene, how 'bout you and I
Charlene, kako bi bilo
havin' a smart cocktail down by the pool?
popijemo jedan koktel dole, kod bazena?
Who is this fool?
Ko je ova budala?
That's a good idea. Just put it on my bill.
To je dobra ideja. Samo stavite na moj racun.
I don't want no smart cocktail. I need your help.
Ne zelim da pijem koktele. Treba mi tvoja pomoc.
Miss.
Gospodjo.
Another martini.
Jos jedan martini.
Oh, hell, no. I know she ain't talkin' to me.
Oo, ne. Znam da ona ne govori meni.
Ashley, she doesn't work here.
Ashiey, ona neradi ovde.
If she isn't here to work, then what is she here for?
Ako neradi ovde, iz kog razloga je onda tu.
Oh, hells no, Miss Thing. You best pump your brakes.
Oo, ne, propustas. Bolje napumpaj malo svoje kocnice.
She's my ex-wife's sister.
Ona je sestra moje bivse zene.
I would have killed her myself years ago.
Trebao sam da je ubijem jos davno.
It's Mrs. Arness!
To je gdja. Arness!
Mmm. Old Iron Ass be lookin' mean.
Mmm. Mislis na ono staro-gvozdje.
Yes. You have to go.
Da, da. Ti moras da ides.
You like raw oysters, Charlene?
Volite li sirove ostrige, Charlene?
Yeah. I guess I can hang out for a bit.
Da, predpostavljam da mogu da izadjem na malo.
They got any hot wings around here?
Da li imaju krilca na zaru ovde?
All right. Whatever you want. Yes.
Uredu. Sta god hoces. Da.
- You give me a place to stay? - Yes.
- Mogu li da spavam kod tebe? - Da.
- And you work on my case? - Around the clock.
- I radices na mom slucaju? - uvek.
I'll leave when you expunge my record.
Otici cu kada slistis moj dosije.
Consider it expunged.
Smatraj da je vec.
All right. I'd like a key, please.
Uredu. Zelela bih kluceve, molim lepo.
Mr. Sanderson?
G. Sanderson?
Mrs. Arness.
Gdjo. Arness.
Who is your associate?
Ko je tvoj pomocnik?
This is Howie Rottman, the attorney I told you about.
Ovo je Howie Rottman, zastupnik o kome sam vam pricao.
A great pleasure to meet you, Mrs. Arness.
Veliko mi je zadovoljstvo, gdjo. Arness.
I meant her.
Mislila sam na nju.
Oh.
Ou.
Her?
Nju?
Her is... her...
Ona je... ona...
She is our... our nanny.
ona je nasa... nasa dadilja.
Dad, I'm bored.
Oce, dosadno mi je.
Kids, how good to see you.
Deco, kako je lepo sto vas vidim.
Don't we just love our nanny, Charlene?
Jeli tako da volimo nasu, dadilju, Charlene?
Uh... Y-yeah.
Uuu... D-Da.
Don't you just love being our nanny, Charlene?
Jeli tako da ti volis sto si nasa dadilja, Charlene?
Yessir.
Da gospodine.
Now I'm gonna go on down to the pool with the child'n.
Sada idem dole na bazen sa decom.
Maybe we make fun of the white folks again, huh, kids?
Mozda opet zbijemo neku salu sa belcima, deco?
Ooh-hoo!
Oo - ho!
Oh, the kids just love her.
Oo, deca je mnogo vole.
- What a sense of humor. - Yeah.
- Kakav smisao za humor. - Da.
Peter, I'm going to hang by the pool.
Peter, idem ja sad do bazena.
If you need me, that's where I'll be.
Ako me trebas, znas gde sam.
Mrs. Arness.
Gdjo. Arness.
Uh, right this way,
Uu, ovuda, gdjo. Arness.
Come, William.
Hajde, wiiiiam.
You have the papers?
Imate li dokumenta?
Oh, yes, yes, I do.
Oo, da, da, imam.
Strange clothes for a nanny.
Cudna odeca za dadilju.
Well, it's a fashion to kids.
Pa da to je moda zbog dece.
- Ow! - William, mind.
- Ouu! - W i i i i a m.
Hello, Sanderson family!
Zdravo, familijo Sanderson!
Georgey, don't forget poker night!
Georgey, nezaboravi noc za poker!
I won't.
Necu.
How could I forget poker night?
Kako mogu to da zaboravim?
I propose a toast.
Zelim da nazdravimo.
Okay.
Dobro.
Mm-hmm.
Mm - hmm.
To us.
Za nas.
May we always...
Mozemo uvek...
- Mmm. - Sorry. It's mine.
- Mmm. - Izvini. Moj je.
Oh, you're not gonna answer that, are you?
Oo, neces valjda da se javis?
Well, it might be... might be one of my kids.
Pa, mozda je... mozda je neko od moje dece.
Just one minute.
Samo jedan minut.
Sorry.
Izvini.
Hello?
Halo?
Hey, it's me.
Hej, ja sam.
Oh, hi, Ashley. Everything okay?
Oo, zdravo, Ashiey. Sve je u redu?
I don't know.
Ne znam.
I saw Peter hanging out at the club today.
Videla sam Peter-a izasao je do kluba, danas.
He was mingling with a large black woman.
Smeskao se sa jednom velikom crnkinjom.
What? What are you talking about?
Sta? O cemu to pricas?
He said it was his nanny.
Rekao je da mu je dadilja.
She didn't look like any nanny I'd ever seen.
Nikada nisam videla takvu dadilju.
She was all... tattooed and welfarish.
Sva je... tetovirana, razbacana, cudno obucena.
It was...
Sva je...
Oh, is that funny to you? Is that funny?
Oo, tebi je to smesno? To je smesno?
Am I funny to you?
Jesam li ti ja smesna?
No, no. That's not funny.
Ne, ne. To nije smesno.
Were you laughing at me?
Da li si se to meni smejala?
Oh, I wasn't...
Oo, nisam...
Stop. Get away.
Stop. Bezi bre.
No, I wasn't laughing at you.
Ne, nisam se smejala tebi.
Just... hang on.
Samo... sacekaj.
Um, you know, look, I know Peter. I know him.
Umm, znas, gledaj, ja znam Peter-a. Znam ga.
He's not gonna spend all his time taking care of the kids.
Nece da odvoji vreme za cuvanje dece.
He went and hired somebody!
On ode i unajmi nekoga!
Seriously, Kate! This woman was no nanny.
Ozbiljno, Kate! Ta zena nije dadilja.
You need to do something.
Moras da uradis nesto.
I saw this woman. I was there.
Videla sam tu zenu. Bila sam tamo, a ti nisi.
Shouldn't you at least be looking at references?
Sigurna si da nisi makar malo videla reference?
Thank you. Thank you.
Hvala ti. Hvala ti.
Listen, Peter is nothing if not responsible.
Slusaj, Peter je nista ako nije odgovoran.
It's not like he's gonna hire a convicted felon.
Nije on takav da unajmi osumljicenog kriminalca.
Oh, I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Oo, ja nebih bas bila toliko sigurna.
Ohh!
Ouu!
Let's see... we got resisting arrest, assaulting an officer,
Da vidimo... opiranje hapsenju, napadanje oficira,
repeated attempts at eye-gouging,
ponavljanje pokusaja...
and... scrotum crushing.
i... lomljenje.
Well, I was a little riled up, being framed and all.
Dobro, izvacarena, i namesteno mi je.
And your clothes and I.D. Were found at the scene.
I tvoja odeca i LK. Koje su nasli na licu mesta.
All plants. I never robbed nobody!
Sva oprema. Nikada nisam opljackala nikog!
Okay.
Uredu.
I know my rights. I get an appeal.
Znam moja prava. Ulozicu zalbu.
I get an appeal!
Ulozicu zalbu!
You only get an appeal if you were convicted and incarcerated.
Mozes da ulozis zalbu ako si optuzena.
You were released.
Oslobodjena.
Look, why don't you just start over?
Gledaj, zasto nepocnes sve ispocetka?
Go back to school and get at least a passing familiarity
Vrati se u skolu i nabavi najmanje popusnicu za usavrsavanje.
With the English language.
Engleskim jezikom.
It's no end to what you can accomplish
Nije kraj za to sto mozes zavrsiti
with a little commitment.
sa malim obavezama.
My daughter Sarah is fully committed,
Moja cerka Sarah je potpuno obavezana,
and she's going places.
i odlazi na mesta.
Oh, she's goin' places, all right.
Ou, i odlazi na mesta, pa dobro.
So, it's a charitable remainder trust.
Dakle, to je dobrotvoran ostatak poverenja.
That way, the old tightwad gets a huge deduction every year.
Tako da, stari cvrsti cep dobija dedukciju svake godine.
Uh, no more calls, Sofia.
Uuu, nema vise poziva, Sofia.
It's not a call. There's someone here...
Nije poziv. Ovde je neko...
Girl, get out!
Zeno, napolje!
I do not know who you are...
Neznam ko ste vi...
Send her in.
Pustite je unutra.
Bet you know me now, huh?
Ha sad me znas, a?
This couldn't wait until tonight?
Nije moglo da saceka do veceras?
Well, well, well!
Vidi, vidi, vidi!
Come in, have a seat, spend some time.
Udjite, izvolite sesti, potrosite malo vremena s'nama
Thanks, homeboy, and, no, it can't wait.
Hvala, domacice, i ne, nemoze da ceka.
You gotta check this out.
Moras ovo da proveris.
- What is it? - I found the deposition.
- Sta je ovo? - Pronasla sam izbaceno...
The prosecution interviewed an eyewitness,
Sudjenje, saslusan je novi svedok.
and she told them that the perpetrator
I ona im je rekla da zlocinac
didn't have a tattoo on the chest.
nije imao tetovazu na grudima.
They never told my lawyer about this shit.
Nikada nisu rekli mom advokatu o ovom sranju.
That's withholding exculp...
To sa zadrzavanjem oprav...
Exculpatory evidence. People vs. Stanley, I know.
opravdani dokaz. Narod protiv Stanley, znam.
How do you know that?
Kako ti to znas?
Why wouldn't she know that? She's got it goin' on.
Zasto nebi to znala? Shvata kako sve ide.
Damn, Pete, all I did in there was read law books.
Prokletstvo Peter, sve sto sam radila tamo je citanje pravnih knjiga.
And with comprehension.
Sa razumevanjem.
Made you think I was a lawyer.
Mozda si mislio da sam advokat.
I mean, you obviously have pockets of intelligence.
Mislim, ti ocigledno imas inteligenciju u dzepu.
So, why do you walk and talk and act the way you do?
Pa, zasto se onda tako ponasas kako se ponasas?
Because it's sexy.
Zato sto je seksi.
It ain't actin'!
Zato sto ne glumim!
This is who I am.
Ovo sam ja.
I mean, you think I can't talk like you?
Mislim, da ti mislis da mogu da pricam kao ti?
Oh, Peter,
Oo Peter,
I absolutely love what you've done with the place!
Ja prosto volim to sto si uradio sa ovim prostorom!
It's so sterile, so... so bland, so wonderful!
Tako je sterilno, tako... izvanredno!
See? You can do it.
Vidis? Ti ti mozes.
Oh, you like that, huh?
Oo, svidelo ti se, ha?
Well, you can kiss my natural black ass,
Onda, mozes slobodno da me poljubis u moju prirodno crnu guzu,
because I don't need your approval.
zato sto mi netreba tvoje odobrenje.
No, she don't need
Ne, njoj ne treba tvoje dopustenje.
Hey, you don't think I compromise the way I act?
Hej, ne mislis da ovakvim ponasanjem trazim kompromis?
You think I like walking around like an uptight... honky?
Mislis da volim da hodam ovako utegnut...?
Yes. I know your lingo.
Da. Znam ja vas recnik.
Peter, Mr. Tobias is coming to see you.
Peter, g. Tobias dolazi da te vidi.
Oh, God.
Oo, boze.
Well, this should be interesting.
Dobro, ovo ce biti interesantno.
Uh-oh. What we gotta do, play "hide the sister"?
Uu - oo. Sta treba da radimo, da se igramo "sakrite sestru"?
Or do I gotta do that slave thing again?
Lli da igram robinju ponovo?
Just... just act natural.
Samo... samo budite prirodni.
- Let's get her out of here. - Why don't we get her out?
- Izvedimo je napolje. - Zasto da je izvedemo napolje?
Peter... Howie.
Peter... Howie.
Ed.
E d.
Who is this?
Ko je ovo?
- Uh, this is the... - Well, we were just having...
- Uu, ovo je... - Pa, mi mi samo imamo...
Well, Mr. Sanderson, I can see you are very busy.
Dobro, g. Sanderson, vidim da ste previse zauzeti.
That's why I really appreciate you
Zato vas i toliko postujem
offering your services free of charge.
sto ste nam ponudili vase usluge besplatno.
Oh, I... well, I just... gosh.
Oo, ja... dobro, ja samo... boze moj.
Peter...
Peter...
Well, see, Mr. Sanderson here,
Dobro, vidite g. Sanderson ovde,
being the heavenly man that he is...
on je bozanstven covek, da takav je...
God bless you!
bog vas blagoslovio!
Oh, you got that anointing on you...
Oo, vi imate to...
...has offered to do the taxes for the Compton Evangelistic
...ponudio je da odradi te takse za evangelisticko
Episcopal Baptist church of South Central.
episkopiju baptisticke crkve juznog centra.
You know, just anything to help
Znate, samo sve da pomognem
Reverend Shack... tillfont.
velecasni Shack... obdelovati krstionicu.
Just call him Shack.
Zovite ga samo Shack.
Shack.
Shack.
Well, I'll let you guys go.
Onda, ja vas ostavljam momci.
I'll see you at choir rehearsal on Thursday.
Vidimo se onda u cetvrtak.
7:00, now!
00, sad!
I'll escort Mrs. Shacktill... font
Ja cu otpratiti gdju Shack do dole
to the elevator.
do lifta.
Gentlemen.
Gospodo.
Uh, Peter, we're really in a crunch.
Uu, Peter, stvarno nam skripi.
I just got word that another firm's in the running
Upravo sam saznao da druga firma pocinje da radi
for the R&S account.
za forther&s racun.
We need to close this deal.
Moramo da zatvorimo taj ugovor.
Look...
Vidite...
I have no problem being Peter's wingman on this one.
Nemam problema otkad je Peter-ov vodeci covek na ovome.
Oh, well, thanks anyway, but I really have it under control,
Oo, dobro, hvala u svakom slucaju, ali ja stvarno drzim sve pod kontrolom,
so, you don't have to worry about a thing, Ed.
ukoliko, vi nemate brige u vezi toga, ed.
Good. Then I'll expect you to wrap it up in a day or two.
Dobro. Onda te ocekujem da mi pokrijes za dan ili dva.
That's the plan, certainly.
To je plan, sigurno.
Ah.
A h.
Well.
Dobro.
Could you...
Mozes li...
- Sure. - Thank you.
- Sigurno. - Hvala.
Thank you.
Hvala vam.
She can't tee up her own ball?
Nece moci ni da udari lopticu?
I've been playing this game for many years...
Igram ovu igru vec duzi niz godina...
That's what it feels like.
Tako se i oseca.
...and it's all about patience.
...i sve je u strpljenju.
Well, you beat me by 19.
Pa, pobedili ste me sa 19.
MRS. ARNESS: Uh, let's make it 20.
Uu, da kazemo 20.
All right.
Uredu.
Mrs. Arness, I was wondering
Gdjo. Arness, pitao sam se
if you'd like to come over to my house on Thursday
ako biste zeleli da dodjete kod mene kuci u cetvrtak
and possibly look over the contract.
i mozemo da bacimo pogled na ugovor.
I'll have to check with my secretary, Julia.
Moram da proverim sa mojom sekretaricom, Julia-om.
Mrs. Arness, would you excuse me for a minute?
Gdjo. Arness, da li biste me izvinuli na minut?
I just have to check on my children.
Samo da proverim decu.
Oh, of course. You do that.
Oo, naravno. Slobodno.
I'd like to dip you in Cheez Whiz
Voleo bih da vam ujmocim u sir fijuk
and spread you over a Ritz Cracker,
i zamahnem te krekerom,
if I'm not being too subtle.
ako nisam mnogo subtilan.
Boy, you are some kind of freaky.
Decko, ti si neka vrsta nakaze
Oh, you have no idea.
Oo, nemas pojma.
You got me straight trippin', boo.
Shvatila si me pogresno.
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, what are you doing here?
Hej, hej, hej! Hej, sta ti radis ovde?
What does it look like? I'm on a date.
Kako ti izgleda? Ja imam sudar.
On a date.
Sudar.
She's on a date? She's a felon.
Ona ima sudar? Ona je kriminalac.
- I am not a felon. - Hey, what is she doing here?
- Ja nisam kriminalac. - Hej, sta ona radi ovde?
Get used to it, Twiggy.
Navikni se nato, grabuljo.
You're gonna be seeing a lot more of me around here.
Vidjaces me jos mnogo puta ovde.
Not without a broom in your hand.
Ne bez tvoje metle u ruci.
If I have, it's 'cause I'm here to sweep up the white trash.
Ako je imam, to je zbog toga da pocitim belo djubre.
Save it for the YMCA, Jemima.
Sacuvaj to za gradsku cistocu.
Bitch! I'm gonna kick the bulimia out of your ass!
Kucka! Razvalicu joj njeno koscato dupe!
Have you ever had a tempered moment?
Jesi li ikad cula za temperamentan trenutak?
Why don't you go back to the vodka bottle you crawled out of?
Zasto se nevratis do tvoje flase Vodke i popijes je na iskap?
Mrs. Arness is here.
Gdja. Arness je ovde.
I am sheltering you. I'm helping you.
Sklanjam te. Pomazem ti.
Remember, I helped you...
Seti se, pomocicu ti...
All right! I'll let it ride.
Uredu! Pusti cu da me odveze.
Thank you for letting it ride. That is wise and mature.
Hvala ti za to. To je mudro i zrelo.
Now, just get her walking that way.
Sada, samo je odvedi u onom pravcu.
Let me show you the place, Charlene.
Dopusti mi da ti pokazem mesto, Charlene.
Looking good, Lois!
Dobro izgledas, Lois!
Hey, freak boy...
Hej, nakazo...
I'm gonna make myself a little more luscious for you, okay?
Idem da se sredim malo sladje za tebe, vazi?
I'll be right back.
Odmah se vracam.
Okay, precious.
Vazi, lepotice.
What are you doin' in here?
Sta ti radis ovde?
I told you you was gonna be seein' more of me, right?
Rekla sam ti da cemo se videti jos, jel tako?
Look, I came here to warn you.
Vidi, dosla sam ovde da te upozorim.
You keep disrespecting me,
Moraces da me postujese,
and it's gonna get rough around here.
i desice se ovde po sobi.
Back off, Shaniqua.
Oladi, shaniqua.
You don't scare me.
Nisi me uplasila.
You know what? That's it.
Znas sta? Sad je dosta.
You must need a little more eye shadow, right? Come on!
Trebace ti jos malo senke za oci, jel tako? Hajde!
You've messed with the wrong W.A.S.P., bitch.
Zakacila si se sa pogresnom osom, kucko.
Compliments of Tae-Bo,
Komplimenti za Tae-bo,
two hours a day, five days a week.
dva sata dnevno, pet dana u nedelji.
Compliments of the 'hood, 24 hours a day, all my life.
Komplimenti iz kraja, 24 sata dnevno, ceo moj zivot.
You know, for a skinny white ho, you're pretty tough.
Znas, za belokosca, dosta si teska.
And I don't ever want to have this conversation again!
I vise nezelim ovakav razgovor ponovo!
"The girl had dou..."
"Devojka ima dv..."
"...ble..."
"...bi..."
"...double D-cups."
"...dve sise."
There you go. You got it, lil' man.
Eto vidis. Ide ti, momcino.
"I put my mouth on her nip..."
"Stavio sam svoja usta na njenu..."
What is that?
Sta je to?
What are you doing letting him read th...
Sto mu bre dajes da cita ovo...
He read. You read.
on cita. Ti citas.
Georgey, you read.
Georgey, ti citas.
I'm gonna kill you!
Ubicu te!
I am so proud of you.
Ponosan sam na tebe.
Pfft. I found it in your drawer.
Pfft. Nasla sam u tvojoj fioci.
Well, I am a grown man of 54... 41... 49 years old,
Dobro, ja sam odrastao covek od 54... 41... 49 starosti,
and he's 8, and what I read in the privacy of my...
i on ima 8, i sta ja citam privatno u svom...
How'd you do it?
Kako ti je uspelo?
Oh, God, I'm never gonna get this done.
Oo, Boze, nikada necu ovo zavrsiti.
Look, the boy don't look carefully
Vidi, decko ne obraca previse paznje
at the details in a word,
na detalje u reci,
so most of the time, he's just guessin'.
neki put samo nagadja.
What you got to do is just slow it down
Sta treba da radis je da ga malo usporis
and give him somethin' stimulatin' to read.
i das mu nesto stimulativno za citanje.
Dad?
Oce?
What's a rack?
Sta je to "arack"?
It's a country.
To je zemlja.
Well...
Dobro...
I was just doin' it 'cause he was botherin' me.
to sam uradila samo zato sto me je gnjavio.
Well, either way...
Dobro, bilo koji nacin...
Can you get rid of this?
Mozes li da se resis ovoga?
Just put it back in my room,
Samo ih ostavi kod mene u sobi,
'cause I'll get rid of it, 'cause I have a special...
da imam nesto za citanje...
Well, Mrs. Kline, how wonderful to see you.
Opa, gdjo. Kiine, kako mi je drago sto vas vidim.
Come in!
Udjite!
It's girls poker night at the house.
Zensko je poker vece u kuci.
Where's my little dealer?
Gde je moj mali trgovac?
Well, just wait right here, and I will just go get him.
Evo samo vi sacekate ovde sada cu ja po njega.
Georgey, Mrs. Kline is here!
Georgey, gdja. Kiine je stigla!
Hi, Mrs. Kline.
Zdravo, gdjo. Kiine.
Come on, Georgey!
Dodji, Georgey!
Tonight, I'm gonna teach you to bluff.
Veceras, cu te nauciti kako se blefira.
And I think we need to comb your hair differently.
I mislim da bi tebalo da ti napravimo drugaciju frizuru.
You look like a fag.
Licis na pedera.
- I'm not a fag! - I didn't say you were.
- Ja nisam peder! - Nisam ni rekla da jesi.
- Hello. - Hi. How are you?
- Zdravo. - Zdravo. Kako ste?
Oh, good evening, sir.
Oo, dobro vece, gospodine.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Cekaj, Cekaj, Cekaj, Cekaj, Cekaj.
Dad, I don't want you to freak out, okay?
Oce, ne zelim da poludis, vazi?
Why would I freak out?
Zasto bih poludeo?
Well...
Pa...
Dad, this is Aaron.
Oce, ovo je Aron.
Hi.
Zdravo.
- Hello. - How do you do, sir?
- Zdravo. - Kako ste, gospodine?
I-I-I'm so glad to actually meet you.
M-m-m meni je drago sto smo se upoznali.
I-I-I told Sarah that it was very important
R-r-rekao sam Sari da je to veoma vazno
that you feel comfortable with me
da se osecate ugodno samnom
taking her to my parents' for dinner.
vodim je kod mojih roditelja na veceru.
So, this is a date?
Dakle, to je sudar?
Oh, um, I'll have her home by 11:00 at the latest, sir?
O, um, dovescu je kuci do 23:00 najkasnije, gospodine?
I guess that'd be all right.
Mislim da ce to biti uredu.
All right. Did it work?
Uredu. Da li je upalilo?
Yeah, like a charm, my friend.
Naravno, sarmirao sam, prijatelju.
All right. Let's party.
Dobro. Idemo u zezanje.
Hey, watch the seats.
Hej, pazite na sedista.
- All right... - Oh, shut up.
- Uredu... - oo, zacepi.
No, I'm serious. It's leather.
Ne bre, ozbiljan sam.
Hmm.
Hmm.
Well, look at you, all growed up.
Pa, pogledaj se, kako si porastao.
There's nothing to eat in the house.
Nemamo nista za jelo u kuci.
Yeah. You comin' to a point?
Dobro. Predji na stvar?
Well, I'm hungry. Are you?
Dobro, ja sam gladan. A ti?
You askin' me out?
Zoves me da izadjemo?
Well, no, I'm not.
Ma, jok ja.
Yes, I am.
Da, zovem te.
Okay.
Vazi.
Oh, look at the legs on this wine.
O, pogledaj nogu na ovoj vinskoj casi.
I'm telling you, this place is bangin'.
Kazem ti ovo mesto je opasno dobro.
Don't you just mean, "This is nice"?
Zar nisi mislila "ovo je fino"?
Why the word "bangin"' make you so uptight?
Zasto te izraz "opasno dobro" cini nelagodnim?
You're smart... if you'd just deign to speak English
Ti si pametna... ako samo krenes da pricas kako treba
with what you learned on the Internet and in prison,
sa onim sto si naucila na internetu i u zatvoru,
you could be a paralegal tomorrow.
mozes da budes nesto kao pravnik sutra.
Like they gonna be beatin' down my door to let me in school.
Mislis da ce me tuci ako ne odem u skolu.
You're exactly the kind of person they want.
Ti si tacno prava osoba koju oni traze.
Well, why would I want to do that, anyway?
Ali, zasto bih ja to uradila?
I've been to your office.
Bila sam u tvojoj kancelariji.
Everybody's all uptight, overworked,
Svi izgledaju utegnuti, prezaposleni,
tired, stressed-out, don't see their family.
umorni, pod stresom, nevidjaju svoju porodicu.
"Ooh, Ed is comin'." "Ooh, Tobias."
"O, Ed dolazi" "O, Tobias"
I get a wedgie just walking in your office.
Sva se ustogljim dok samo dodjem do tvoje kancelarije.
Hey, it's what people do. They work.
Hej, to je ono sto ljudi radi. Oni rade.
Look, all I'm sayin' is I did the confinement thing
Vidi, ja samo kazem ja sam ogranicila mentalne stvarcice
for four years.
cetiri pune godine.
If you're so concerned with my future,
Ako si toliko zabrinut za moju buducnost,
just help me clear my name.
samo mi pomozi da skinem ljagu s'mog imena.
I got it from there.
Dobila sam ga odande.
I got my own dreams, my own goals.
Imam ja svoje snove, svoje ciljeve u zivotu.
Hey, give it to me.
- Hej, daj mi to.
Hey! What'd you do that for?!
Hej! Zasto si to uradila?!
- 'Cause you work too much. - This is my phone!
- Zato sto radis previse. - To je moj telefon!
That's probably why your wife left your sorry ass.
To je verovatno i razlog zasto ti je zivot okrenuo ledja.
Okay, Oprah, if you're so good at relationships,
Dobro, oprah, ako si ti tako dobra s'vezama,
how come you don't have a boyfriend?
kako to da nemas decka?
I had one.
Lmala sam.
It's just I haven't seen or heard from him
Samo sto se nisam cula snjim
since I went in four years ago.
otkad je otisao pre cetiri godine.
Were you in love with him?
Bila si zaljubljena u njega?
Come on, let's go dance.
Hajde da igramo.
Ha ha ha ha... no.
Ha ha ha ha... ne.
Come on. When is the last time you danced?
Hajde bre. Kada si poslednji put igrao?
At my wedding.
Na svojoj svadbi.
Don't worry, I can dance. It's just that I don't wanna.
Nebrini se umem da igram. Ali samo to nezelim.
Come on, smooth. Show me what you're workin' with.
Hajde, otmeni. Pokazi mi sta ti to znas.
I can dance. I just don't want to dance.
Umem da igram. Samo ne zelim.
Man, you can't dance.
Covece, ti neznas da igras.
- Well, I got moves. - Let me see.
- Pa, imam te pokrete. - Pokazi se.
All right, all right.
Uredu, uredu.
Okay, one last little drink here.
Vazi, evo sam da cugnem jos malo.
What, you got to pee?
Sta je bre, piski ti se?
This was big in high school.
Ovo je bilo in u srednjoj skoli.
Man, look, you can't dance from your brain.
Covece, gledaj, ne mozes da igras mozgom.
You gotta feel it. Now, come on.
Moras da osetis. Sad, hajde.
Show me how you made them kids.
Pokazi mi kako si napravio decu.
- What the hell... - How's this?
- Sta je bre ovo... - Jel, dobro?
That's great for an epileptic. Come on, now.
Dobro je za epilepticare. Hajde, sada.
You gotta move your pelvis with it.
Moras da imas taj rad kukovima.
More hips. There you go.
Vise bokove. E tako.
Get smooth with it.
Samo opusteno, tako.
Well, I'm sorry. I can't help it. I miss him.
Znas, zao mi je. Ne mogu da mu pomognem. Nedostaje mi.
Oh, snap out of it, already.
O, raspukni se, vec.
I'm snapped. I'm snappy.
Pukla sam skroz.
Oh, God, Ash.
O, boze, ash.
I still can't believe you were hit by a car.
Nemogu da verujem da su te udarila kola.
Did you call a lawyer?
Jesi li zvala advokata?
Oh, I can't talk to a lawyer. I was jaywalking.
O, nemogu da zovem advokata. Na uslovnom sam.
So, can we just stop...
Tako, mozemo li da prestanemo...
- What? - Oh, my God.
- Sta? - O, moj boze.
What?
Stat?
Look at that!
Pogledaj!
Oh, my God, it's true. Look at that! Look at that!
O, moj boze, istina je. Pogledaj! Pogledaj!
He never danced like that with me.
Nikada nije igrao samnom ovako.
I'm gonna go talk to him.
Idem da popricam sa njim.
No! Sit!
Ne! Sedi! N o! S it!
Why?
Zasto?
I can't tell you.
Nemogu da ti kazem.
If I talk about it,
Ako ti ispricam,
gangster people will come to my house and cut me.
gangsteri ce me izmasakrirati.
Oh.
Oou.
Oh, he almost looks like a fun person.
O, izgleda skoro kao srecna osoba.
Must've been me.
Mora da bude samnom
No. Stop beating yourself up. It's him.
Ne. Prestani da krivis sebe. To je on.
Can we just get out of here? Now?
Mozemo li da odemo odavde? Sada?
You know what they say...
Znas li sta kazu...
once you go black, you never go back.
jednom odes sa crnom, nikada se vise nevratis.
Can we get the check, please?
Mozemo li dobiti racun, molim?
And that's why I worked so hard,
I eto zasto ja radim toliko naporno,
so I could give Kate a good life, then it backfired!
mogu da pruzim Kate dobar zivot...
Man, bitches don't care nothin' about that shit.
Covece, kuckama nije stalo do tih sranja.
Oh, bitches do too care.
Oo, kuckama je stalo.
I'm gonna tell you a secret...
Sada cu ti otkriti tajnu...
sometimes I drive by our old house, and I just look at it,
povremeno odem do nase kuce, i gledam je.
and I just remember our life, and it just hurts!
I setim se kako smo ziveli, a to boli!
Man, that is so pathetic, P. Diddy.
Covece, to je tako pateticno.
But you know what? I'm gonna help you get her back.
Samo znas sta? Pomocicu ti da ti se vrati.
How?
Kako?
Well, first, we gotta create a mood.
Dobro, prvo, moramo da napravimo raspolozenje.
Just like at the restaurant, baby.
Isto kao u restoranu, duso.
I'm already there.
Vec sam tamo.
Yeah. Now, feel the Barry.
Daaa. A sad, oseti Barry.
Feel Barry White. Talk like Barry.
Oseti Barry beli. Pricaj kao barry.
- Okay, that's Barry. - Yeah.
- To, to je Barry. - Daa.
This is Kate.
Ovo je Kate.
Hey, Kate. Yeah.
Hej, Kate. Daa.
I want you to talk nasty to her!
Hocu da pricas prljavo s'njom.
Talk nasty!
Prljavoo!
I'd like to kiss you a lot.
Hocu da te ljubim puno.
Cut that sensitive shit, Nancy Boy!
Izbaci ta senzitivna sranja, glupanderu!
What?
Sta sad?
- You gotta be a beast! - A beast!
- Moras biti zver! - Zver!
Yeah!
Daaa!
In the bedroom, a woman wants a man
U spavacoj sobi zena hoce muskarca
that knows how to ride her when she bucks.
koji zna kako da je jasi dok ona brblja.
Ride 'em when she bucks! Ride 'em!
Jase je dok ona brblja! Jase je!
It's just... I can't. It's a sculpture. I just can't.
Jednostavno... nemogu. Ovo je skulptura... nemogu.
All right, okay.
Uredu, vazi.
Use me, then.
Probaj na meni.
Huh?
Huu?
Damn it, grab these.
Prokletstvo, zgrabi ih.
- What?! - Grab 'em!
- Molim?! - Zgrabi ih!
Ohh!
Ooo!
Oh, I get it, yeah.
Ooo, shvatam, daa.
- Hey, Kate. - Uh-huh.
- Hej, Kate. - Uu - huu.
Yeah, you've been waitin' for this for a while, huh?
Daa, cekala si na ovo dugo, haa?
That's right. Now, what you gonna do to her?
Tako je. Sad, sta biste vi radili?
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do!
Sad cu da ti kazem sta cu da uradim.
I'm gonna give you an aromatherapy massage
Dacu ti aroma terapiju masaze.
with incense!
Sa potpalom!
No! Come on, now!
Ne! Hajde, sad!
Wimps give aromatherapy massages!
Kakvo bre davanje aroma terapijska masaza!
Tell her again!
Reci joj ponovo!
All right!
Uredu!
I'm gonna have...
Sada cu da ti dam...
sexual intercourse, baby!
casove seksa, duso!
No, you... you a beast! You need some of these.
Ne, ti... ti si zver! Treba ti nesto od ovih.
- Yeah. - Cojones grande!
- Daa. - Cojones grande!
Yeah! I'm gonna put 'em in my pants!
Daa! Stavi cu ih u pantalone!
- Get in there, boys! - Now, grab 'em!
- Upadajte, momci! - Sada, zgrabi ih!
- Grab 'em. Yeah, hey, baby! - Grab 'em!
- Zgrabi ih. Daa, hej, duso! - Zgrabi ih!
Now, what you gonna do? What you gonna do?!
A sad, sta ces da uradis? Sta ces da uradis?!
Yeah, Mama! You gonna be my tawdry little woman?
Daaa, mama! Sada ces mi biti mala vristalica?
Damn right! Now get to humpin'!
Prokleto upravu! A sada zaskoci!
- How 'bout that, huh?! - Yeah!
- Kakva nastup, haa?! - Daaa!
How would you like me to pounce on you
Kako ti se svidja kada se bacam na tebe?
- like a lion from above? - I like it! I like it!
- Volim vise od preko? - Svidja mi se! Svidja mi se!
- Yo! - That's what I'm talkin'!
- Yo! - O tome ti i pricam '!
You ain't just no king of the jungle,
Ti nisi samo kralj dzungle,
you own that jungle!
ti si ta dzungla!
That's your pride!
To je tvoj ponos!
You own that jungle, and ain't no one
Ti posedujes tu dzunglu i niko
gonna come around and mess with your pride!
nemoze da se zeza sa tvojim ponosom!
That's right! I like that.
Tako je! Svidja mi se.
Yeah! You ain't ready for that shit! Come on, now!
Daa! Nisi spreman za to sranje! Hajde, sad!
Be a beast! What you gonna do when she starts ridin', huh?
Budi zver! Sta ces da radis kada ona zajase, haa?
Take care of her! That's what I'm gonna do!
Da se brines o njoj! Eto sta! Sta cu da radim!
- Uh-huh! Uh-huh! - You're mine, Kate!
- U - huu! Uh - huu! - Ti si moja, Kate!
- Ride that lighting rod! - You don't need these no more.
- Jasi samo tako! - Netreba ti vise ovo.
You got your own! You found your balls!
Imas svoja! Pronasao si svoja jaja!
Yeah, I don't need those balls! I got my own balls!
Daa, netrebaju mi ta jaja! Lmam ja svoja!
Mandingo!
Mandingo!
What goes on in your personal life is none of our business,
Ono sto se desava u tvom privatnom zivotu nije nasa stvar,
but if it begins to affect the firm,
ali kada pocne da utice na firmu,
we need to call attention to it.
onda moramo da obratimo paznju.
Guys, we were moving a statue,
Momci, mi smo pomerali statuu,
and we lost our footing, and we fell.
i jednostavno smo izgubili ravnotezu, i pali smo.
My sister's under the impression
Moja sestra je jos uvek pod utiskom
that you were humping your nanny.
da ste vi zaskocili svoju dadilju.
I was not humping my nanny!
Ja nisam zaskocio svoju dadilju!
Peter, surely you understand that if Mrs. Arness
Peter, sigurno razumes da ako gdja Arness
were to suspect any instability on your part...
posumlja u bilo kakvu nestabilnost kod vas...
There is no instability in my home.
Ne postoji nikakva nestabilnost u mojoj kuci.
You sure you can trust this guy?
Sigurna si da verujes tom liku?
Well, hey, he's helping me reopen my case.
Dobro, hej, pomaze mi da ponovo otvori slucaj.
Y'all got any leads?
Imas ni nesto glavno?
Well, a still from the bank surveillance camera
Dobro, jos uvek sigurnosna kamera banke
is on its way here,
je tamo,
and we found a deposition that could help.
i nasli smo izbacivanje koje bi trebalo pomoci.
Well, that's cool, baby.
Dobro, to je opusteno, duso.
If there's anything I can do to help,
Jel mogu nekako da ti pomognem,
anything... you just holler.
bilo sta... samo zovi.
I gotta run.
Moram da palim.
Hey, Widow, if you meant what you just said,
Hej, Widow, ako si mislio to sto si rekao,
it's not gonna be an easy job.
to nece biti lak posao.
I know it ain't.
Znam da nije.
I just gotta know that if things get rough,
Hocu samo da znam ako nesto iskrsne,
you're not gonna run out on me.
da neces da pobegnes od mene.
I've been waitin' four years for this.
Cekam ovo cetiri godine.
I ain't gonna mess up.
Necu da zabrljam.
Planning another heist?
Planiras li jo jednom?
No. Why would you say that?
Ne. Zasto si to rekao?
I don't know.
Neznam.
Maybe it was hearing the words "job" and "hot"
Mozda zato sto sam cuo reci "posao" i "vruce"
bandied between two tattooed people?
izmedju dvoje tetoviranih?
That was just my old boyfriend I told you about... Widow.
To je samo moj bivsi decko pricala sam ti o tome... Widow.
He's just tryin' to get back with me.
On samo pokusava da mi se vrati.
Mm-hmm.
Mm - hmm.
I'm tellin' you the truth!
Govorim ti istinu!
Look, I just didn't want you to see him,
Vidi, samo nisam zelela da ga vidis,
because Widow, he ain't been the best boyfriend,
zato sto on nije bas najbolji decko,
Now you suddenly care what I think?
Kako ti je iznenada stalo sta ja mislim?
No.
Ne.
Maybe.
Mozda.
A little bit.
Malo da.
No more late visits?
Nema vise kasnih poseta?
Word.
Casna.
Convicted felon's honor?
Osumljicena kriminalna casna?
Innocent convicted felon's honor.
Nevino osumljicena kriminalna casna.
Now, give me some dap, right there on the edge.
Sad, daj mi malodesnu na kraju.
Right there, and then come up here like that.
E tako, i onda od gore ovako.
Pow, like that.
- Pow, ovako.
Hello?
Halo?
Dad!
Oce!
Hey, sweetie.
Zdravo, slatkisu.
Is Charlene there?
Jeli Charlene tu?
Yeah, she's here. Do you want to talk to her?
Da, tu je. Hoces s'njom da pricas?
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm...
- Jesi li dobro? - Da, ja sam...
All right.
dobro.
- Sarah? Okay. - Girl talk.
- Sarah? Da. - Zenske stvari.
What up, dog?
Sta ima, keru?
I need you to come pick me up. I can't talk about it right now.
Treba da me pokupis. Nemogu da pricam sada o tome.
Where you at?
Gde si?
I'm on the corner of Venice and Canal,
Na uglu Venice i Canal,
and there's a whole lot of people out front.
i ima puno ljudi napolju.
- Please don't tell my dad! - All right.
- Molim te nemoj da kazes mom ocu! - Uredu.
No, just calm down. I'm comin' to get you.
Ne, samo se smiri. Dolazim po tebe.
I'm sorry. I didn't know who else to call.
Zao mi je. Nisam znala koga da pozovem.
It's cool. What's goin' on?
Ma opusteno. Sta se desava?
Hey, Sarah, what have you been up to? Hee hee!
Hej, Sarah, sta se desava? Hii hii!
Is that your boyfriend?
To je tvoj decko?
No, he's not my boyfriend.
Ne, nije moj decko.
I liked his friend, Mike,
Svidja mi se njegov prijatelj, Mike,
and we hung out a few times, and he was always really nice,
i izasli smo na par puta, a stalno je bio bas fin,
but then... all he wanted to do tonight was have sex,
ali onda... sve sto je hteo bio je seks,
I mean, he moved in kind of rough, and...
mislim, odjednom je postao surov, i...
He got rough with you? Where he at?
bio je surov prema tebi? Gde je sad?
He went back there with that group.
Otisao je nazad sa onom grupom.
Go wait downstairs.
Idi cekaj me kod stepenica.
Yo, Mike!
Yo, Mike!
Please, don't kill me!
Molim te, nemoj da me ubijes!
Oh, God!
Oo, Boze!
What are you? Crazy?!
Sta si ti? Ludak?
Pull me up! What do you want?!
Podigni me! Sta hoces!
Sarah!
Sarah!
Mike has somethin' to say to you.
Mika ima nesto da ti kaze.
Say "sorry"!
Reci "izvini"!
I-I'm sorry! I'm sorry! God, I am sorry!
L-izvini! Lzvini! Boze, zao mi je!
Say "No means no."
Reci "ne znaci ne."
No means no!
Ne znaci ne!
She was where?!
Bila je gde?!
Calm down. It's just...
Smiri se. Samo... C a i m d own. It' s j u s t...
- She is 14! - She's 15! Wait!
- Ona ima 14! - Ona ima 15! Cekaj!
G... well... oh!
G... onda... oou!
Look...
Vidi...
Sarah don't need a warden.
sarah netreba grdnju.
She needs her father... you...
Ona treba oca... tebe...
so you can't get mad, all right?
zato nemoj da budes besan, dobro?
You do it, she'll never tell you anything again.
Ako to uradis, nece ti vise nikada reci nista.
All right. I get it. I get it.
Uredu. Shvatam. Shvatam.
Just be cool. Just play it cool, you know what I mean?
Samo budi opusten. Opusteno, znas sta to znaci?
Just listen to her. Let her do the talkin'.
Samo je slusaj. Pusti je da prica.
I am listening to you!
Ja slusam tebe!
Thank you.
Hvala ti.
Don't trip.
Nemoj da tripujes.
So...
Dakle...
you went out with a boy...
izasla si sa deckom...
and he took you to a party,
i odveo te je na zurku,
where kids were... drinking
Gde su ostali... pili
and "trippin' on E."...
i "tripovali se."...
and then he took you up to a room
i onda te je odveo gore u sobu
where he tried to...
gde je pokusao da...
"get all up in that..."
"da te skine..."
which he... didn't?
koji... nije?
And then Charlene came...
I onda je Charlene dosla...
in my new car... and brought you home
u mojim novim kolima... i dovezla te kuci
after first... "bitchslapping" him.
posle prve... naucila ga pameti...
Well...
Onda...
...that was some night.
...onda je to nesto.
Oh, Dad!
O, oce!
I can't believe you're not killing me!
Ne mogu da verujem da me nisi ubio!
Oh! This is so great! I want everything out in the open!
O! Tako je divno!
Oh, I have so much more to tell you!
O, imam toliko toga da ti ispricam?
Kate, what are you doing here?
Kate, sta ti radis ovde?
W-What are you doing here?
S-sta ti radis ovde?
It's my shortcut home from work.
Ovo mi je precica do kuce.
No, it's not.
Ne nije.
- Yes, it is. - Is not.
- Da jeste. - Ne nije.
I thought you were in the mountains.
Mislio sam da si na planini.
Well, yeah, I-I came back early.
Pa, da, v-vratila sam se malo ranije.
There were bears that were mauling the campers
Medvedi su poceli da napadaju kampere
and eating them.
i jedu ih.
Wow.
Wow.
But other than that... nothing went wrong with your...
Izmedju ostalog... jel nesto nije u redu sa tvojim...
Oh, no, no. He's great.
o, ne, ne. On je odlicno.
Yeah, I liked him.
Daa, svidja mi se.
So, how's your...
Dakle, kako tvoja...
My what?
moja sta?
Your life?
Tvoj zivot?
Anything hip and new?
Lma li sta novo?
No.
Ne.
Um...
Umm...
I'm having a good time with the kids.
Provodim odlicno vreme sa decom.
Good. Glad you're having fun with her.
Odlicno. Drago mi je da se lepo zabavljas sa njom.
Them.
Njima.
What?
Sta?
You look, um...
Lzgledas, um...
Yeah.
Daa.
Rested.
Odmoreno.
Nice. You look nice.
Slatko. Izgledas slatko.
So, um, I guess I'll come by later and pick up the kids.
Onda, um, predpostavljam da cu doci malo kasnije da pokupim decu.
Oh, I was wondering if I could keep them through Friday.
O, pitao sam se mogu li ih zadrzati do petka.
Really? You're not too busy?
Stvarno? Nisi zauzet?
No.
Ne.
Well, yes, it's okay.
Onda, da, uredu je.
It's wonderful, Peter.
To je predivno, Peter.
You know, if you wanted to come ov...
Znas, ako zelis da dodj... Yo u k n ow, if y o u wa n t e d t o c o m e o v...
Go ahead.
Slobodno.
Sorry.
Izvini.
Hello?
Halo?
Yo, get your butt home, dog.
Yo, dovlaci svoje dupe, keru.
I will be home in my own sweet time, girlfriend.
Bicu kuci kada to ja pozelim, devojko.
You gotta come now. Arness said she on her way over here.
Moras odmah da dodjes. Arness je rekla da je na putu ka nama.
Oh, I forgot all about that.
O, potpuno sam zaboravio na to.
Oh, I'm sorry. I-I have to go.
O, zao mi je. M-m-moram da krenem.
I just forgot about something,
Zaboravio sam nesto,
but I want to continue this conversation,
Ali zelim da nastavimo ovaj razgovor,
so I will call you, or you can call me on my cell.
tako da cu te zvati, ili ti mozes mene za mobilni.
Bye!
Zbogom!
- Is she here yet? - No!
- Jeli stigla? - Nije!
The place is a mess!
Stan je u neredu!
e gotta clean this place up!
Moramo da ocistimo ovaj stan brzo!
Hey, get upstairs and get ready!
Hej, penjite se gore i spremite se!
And what are you reading?!
I sta to citas A n d wh a t a re y o u rea d i n g?!
Get up there! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Dizi se! Ajde! Ajde! Ajde! Ajde! Ajde!
Hey, yo, P., while we got this minute...
Hej, yo, pile., dok imamo jos minut...
there's somethin' I really been meanin' to tell you...
nesto sam stvarno htela da ti kazem...
Well, you'll have to wait.
Dobro, moraces da sacekas.
Kids! She's here!
Deco ona je stigla!
Mrs. Arness?
Gdjo. Arness?
Oh!
Oh!
I'll get right to the point, Mr. Sanderson.
Preci cu odmah na stvar, g. Sanderson.
There are rumors circulating
Kruze neke glasine
that your personal life and your home are in disarray,
da je u vasem privatnom zivotu kao i vasoj kuci vlada nered,
and this makes me feel very unsettled.
i to me je veoma uzdrmalo.
I don't know who misinformed you, but please, come in.
Neznam ko vas je to dezinformisao, ali molim vas udjite.
I'd hate to think you're under any misapprehension
Nevolim da mislim da ste pod uticajem tudjih izmisljotina
about me or my family.
o meni i mojoj porodici.
Sarah? Georgey?
Sarah? Georgey?
You remember Mrs. Arness?
Secate se gdje Arness?
So lovely to see you again.
Toliko na je drago sto vas vidimo opet.
Um, Father, when you have a moment,
Um, oce, kada budes imao vremena,
would you mind helping me with my report on Queen Victoria?
hoces li da mi pomognes u vezi mog izvestaja o kraljici Viktoriji?
Sure, kitten.
Naravno, dete.
And don't forget, Pop, tomorrow you have to come to school
I nemoj da zaboravis, cale, da sutra dodjes u skolu
and help hand out the food to the poor kids.
i pomognes nam oko hrane za siromasnu decu.
Have I ever forgotten to help the poor kids?
Jesam li ikada zaboravio da pomognem siromasnoj deci?
No, Pop. Never.
Ne, cale. Nikada.
In truth, Mr. Sanderson, you have a lovely home.
Iskreno, g. Sanderson, imate stvarno divan dom.
Thank you.
Hvala vam.
And your children are very well-behaved.
I vasa deca se jako lepo ponasaju.
They're angels.
Oni su andjeli.
Oh, William.
Oo, wiiiiam.
Oh, look!
Oo, vidite!
He's even taken a fancy to your boy.
Dopao mu se vas decak.
That's so sweet.
Kako je to slatko.
Anyway, we can go to the den and get the contracts...
U svakom slucaju, mozemo da odemo u sobu i pogledamo ugovor...
What is that heavenly smell?
sta li to samo tako bozanstveno mirise?
Ah, that would be Charlene preparing dinner.
Aa, to mora da Charlene priprema veceru.
Anyway, the contracts...
U svakom slucaju, ugovori...
I haven't smelled home cooking like that since I was a child.
Nisam mirisala ovakvo kuvanje, jos kao dete.
Really? Anyway...
Stvarno? U svakom slucaju...
Brings back such happy memories.
vraca mi tako srecne trenutke.
Does it? Anyway, actually, the den is closer...
Stvarno? U svakom slucaju, zapravo...
Your table looks so inviting.
vas sto izgleda tako izazovno.
Yes. It's too bad it's so small.
Daa. Samo steta sto je tako mali.
Small?
Mali?
Well, actually, it's big, isn't it?
Dobro, zapravo, je veliki, zar ne?
It's a big table, so...
Veliki sto, dakle...
there would be room for one more.
bice mesta za jos jednog.
Oh, well, if it's not an imposition...
O, dobro, ali ako niste u poziciji...
Oh... oh.
ou... ou.
Well, let me just go check if there's enough food.
Dobro, sacekajte samo da proverim ima li dovoljno hrane.
I'm not... I'm not sure,
Nisa... nisam bas siguran,
because, uh, actually, this is the night of, uh,
Zato sto, uf, zapravo, ovo je noc, uf,
Yiminum, the, uh... the holiday where
yiminum, pra..., uf... praznik gde...
white people eat very little portions
beli ljudi jedu veoma male porcije
because that was the night the Lord came down,
zato sto je to noc kada je gospod bog sisao na zemlju,
and he was given food,
i dao nam hranu,
and there was just too much, and he said, "No."
i bilo je bas mnogo, i on je rekao, "nee".
And so, he had a smaller portion,
I tako, je imao malu porciju,
and that's why we might not have enough.
i zato se nama cini uvek da imamo malo.
So, I'll just go check on, uh, what the Lord would say.
Tako da, idem da proverim, uf, sta ce gospod bog da kaze.
Just one second.
Samo sekund.
Come here, William.
Dodji, wiiiiam.
Hey, come here. Are you hungry?
Hej, dodji. Jesi li gladan?
Charlene...
Charlene...
If there was ever a time I needed a favor, it's now.
ako je postojala potreba da mi ucinis uslugu onda je to sad
You got it, baby. Anything.
Dobro, duso. Sta god
Oh, thank you!
Oo, hvala ti!
Oh. Mrs. Arness?
Oo. Gdjo. Arness?
Yes? Oh, yes.
Da? Oo, da.
My family and I are pleased to invite you for dinner.
Moja porodica i ja vas sa zadovoljstvom pozivamo na veceru.
Yeah, oh.
Daa, ou.
Well, very well. I wasn't expecting this.
Dobro, veoma dobro. Nisam ocekivala.
Uh, but if you insist.
Uu, ali ako insistirate.
And then afterwards, we can sign the contracts.
I onda posle toga mozemo da potpisemo ugovor.
Of course.
Naravno.
Dinner is served.
Vecera je servirana.
I was raised in the South, you know.
Odrasla sam na jugu, znate.
That smells just like our Ivy's jambalaya.
Taj miris je isti kao nas ivy' s jambaiaya.
She was so wonderful.
Bila je tako predivna.
We paid her nothing, of course, you know.
Nismo joj placali nista, naravno, znate.
But, then, people had standards of service in those days.
Ali tada su ljudi imali standarda u vezi posluge.
And, of course, Ivy did know
I, naravno, lvy nije znala
that you serve from the left and collect from the right.
da se servira sa leve a kupi sa desne strane.
Don't...
Nemojte...
stop at that story, because I love hearing about your past.
da prekinete tu pricu, zato sto bih voleo da cujem vasu proslost.
That is fascinating.
To je fascinantno.
Oh, yes.
Oo, da.
Well, anyway, as I was saying...
Dobro, u svakom slucaju, kao sto sam rekla...
Yeah.
Daa.
Yeah. Fast-actin'.
Daa. Brzo-delujuci.
Fast-actin'.
Brzo-delujuci.
Ooh, I'm gonna get you.
Ooo, sada ces ti da vidis.
I'm gonna get you.
Sredicu te.
Uh-huh. I'll serve your food right.
Uu - huu. Serviracu vam hrano desno.
Was it the left? Was it the right?
Bilo je levo? Bilo je desno?
Father's work with the Pasadena Republican Youth Group
Otac radi sa "pasadena repubiican" mladima
has truly been invaluable.
stvarno je dragocen.
I hope y'all brought y'all appetites.
Nadam se da ste poneli apetit.
Oh, yes.
Oo, daa.
I brought mine.
Ja sam svoj poneo.
Oh, my goodness.
Oo, boze moj.
This is much too much for me.
Ovo je bas previse za mene.
I'll never get through all that.
Nikada mi neuspeva da sve...
I have a little less here. I'll trade with you.
Ja imam malo manje. Menjacu se sa vama.
Oh.
Ooo.
Thank you.
Hvala vam.
What, Charlene?
Molim, Charlene?
Nothing, sir.
Nista, gospodine.
Oh.
Oo.
Oh, this food is so delicious.
O, ova hrana je tako izvrsna.
You're very lucky to have found such talented help.
Veoma ste srecni sto ste nasli tako talentovanu pomoc.
Well, our Ivy was with us for so long,
Naravno, nasa lvy je bila sa nama veoma dugo,
we really thought of her as one of the family.
smatrali smo je kao clana porodice.
Mmm.
Mmm.
And after every meal,
I posle svakog obroka,
my mother would scrape all the food we hadn't eaten
moja majka je sastrugala statak hrane koji nismo pojeli
and put it on one big plate and give it to Ivy.
stavili na jedan veliki tanjir i dali lvy da jede.
Charlene...
Charlene...
what is that particular taste?
koji je ovo karakteristican ukus?
It's familiar, yet...
Deluje mi poznato...
Is it some kind of herb like sage?
da nije neka travka kao zalfija?
No, it's sort of more like a milk of mint.
Ne, to je vise sorta milko-minta.
Milk of... whatever it is, the taste is explosive.
Milko od... sta god da je, ukus je eksplozivan.
Mmm.
Mmm.
Well, good, then.
Dobro, onda. W e i i, g o o d, t h e n.
Enjoy.
Uzivaj.
Oh, just one moment.
Oo, samo jedan trenutak.
Uh, you know, uh,
Uu, znate, uu,
there's a lovely, sad Negro spiritual...
ima jedna lepa tuzna crnacka spiritualna...
...that Ivy's brother used...
...koju je lvy brat pevao...
Are you all right?
da li si ti dobro? A re y o u a i i ri g h t?
Anyway, Ivy's brother used to sing this
U svako slucaju, lvy brat je pevao
when he came in from the tobacco fields.
kada dolazi sa polja duvana.
Now, there's a second verse
Sada ima druga verzija
if you'd like to join in the chorus.
ako vi hocete da se pridruzite u hor.
Dad?
Oce?
Are you okay?
Jesi li dobro?
I hope your father's all right.
Nadam se da je vas otac dobro.
Does this happen often?
Da li se ovo desava cesto?
Well, if you'll excuse us.
Dobro, Ako biste na izvinuli.
Um...
Um...
Georgey, let's go watch that biography on Francis Drake.
Georgey, hajde da pogledamo biografiju Francis Drake-a.
he seemed to be so moved by that song.
Mora da ga je dirnula ta pesma.
Oh, he movin', all right.
O...
- And tonight's top story... - William?
- I vecerasnje top vesti... - wiiiiam?
The FBI needs your help
FBI trazi vasu pomoc
in finding fugitive at large Charlene Morton.
da pronadje begunca, veliku Charlene Morton.
Charlene is an African-American female, 31 years of age...
Charlene je afro-amerikanka, 31 godina starosti...
What is it?
Sta je to?
...and 5'6", 175 pounds,
...i 170 visoka, 95 kg,
with a tattoo on her left breast.
sa tetovazom na grudima.
Convicted of armed robbery,
Optuzena za pljacku.
Charlene is considered cunning and highly dangerous.
Charlene je lukava, vesta i opasna.
Having escaped from the Women's Correctional Facility
Pobegla je iz popravne ustanove za zene
outside Los Angeles a mere six days ago,
na ulicama LA je vec sest dana,
Morton is suspected to be armed.
sumnjamo da je naoruzana.
This bank surveillance tape shows Charlene wielding a gun
Ova kasete sigurnosne kamere iz banke pokazuje na Charlene kako drzi oruzje
and holding a customer hostage.
i drzi musteriju kao taoca.
Charlene is considered dangerous and may be armed.
Charlene je izuzetno opasna i mozda naoruzana.
If you have any information concerning Charlene Morton,
Ako imate bilo kakvu informaciju o Charlene Morton,
please contact your local FBI office.
molimo vas da kontaktirate vasu lokalnu FBI kancelariju.
That's it for tonight's edition of "Criminals at Large."
To bi bilo sve za veceras u emisiji "Kriminal pod lupom"
Good night and be safe.
Laku noc i cuvajte se.
Mrs. Arness, I can explain everything.
Gdjo. Arness, mogu da objasnim sve.
Pete, before you lose it, just let me explain.
Peter, pre nego sto se izgubis, samo da ti objasnim.
There's nothing to say.
Nema sta da se kaze.
But I didn't do it, Pete.
Ali ja nisam to uradila, Peter.
You have to get out.
Moras da odes.
All right. I'll get my stuff.
Uredu. Idem po stvari.
I don't understand. You saw her and where is she?
Nerazumem. Video si je i gde je ona?
I don't know where she is.
Nemam pojma gde je?
Don't drop the soap.
Nemoj da ti isklizne sapun.
What the hell does that mean?
Sta to treba da znaci?
I just don't believe this. I'm worried about her.
Ja samo samo neverujem u ovo. Brinem se za nju.
I hate the fact that she's out there all alone.
Mrzim cinjenice ali ona je otisla i sada je sama.
You're worried about the poor, innocent, frail creature
Ti brines za jadno, nevino, nezno cudoviste
who can hardly take care of herself on the street?
koje se tesko snalazi na ulici?
What about me? Tobias is gonna fire me!
A sta je samnom? Tobias otpustice me!
And another goody...
I jos jedna dobra stvar...
if Arness calls the cops, I could go to jail!
Ako gdja Arness zove policiju, mogu da odem u zatvor!
Here's the local number for the Bureau.
Evo lokalnog broja FBI.
The FBI takes harboring a fugitive very seriously.
FBI mora pronaci begunca i njegovo skloniste.
You, gentlemen, will be the first to hear from me.
Gospodo, bicete prvi koji ce to saznati od mene.
Arness didn't call the cops, she called the FBI.
Arness nije pozvala pandure, pozvala je FBI.
- Now, you haven't seen me. - I have seen you.
- Sada, nisi me video. - Ali video sam te.
No, I mean, you haven't seen me.
Ne, mislim, nisi me video.
I'm looking right at you. What are you...
Ali upravo te gledam.
If you do hear from her,
Ako se cujes s'njom,
please tell her the cool points are out the window and...
molim te joj reci da je poenta napolju kroz prozor i...
she's got me all twisted up in the game.
dobice obrok uvrnut u igri.
Why you messin' with Lene?
Zasto se mesas sa Lene?
I'm not messing with her, I'm helping her.
Ja se nemesam s'njom, ja joj pomazem.
Bullshit!
Seres!
Uh! I'm telling you the truth!
Uu! Govorim ti istinu!
Listen up. You do not reopen this case.
Slusaj. Nemoj slucajno da ponovo otvaras taj slucaj.
From now on, I'm handlin' it for her.
Od sada ja cu joj pomagati.
I'm not gonna reopen the case. The case is closed.
Necu da ponovo otvorim slucaj. Slucaj je zatvoren.
Stay out of her life.
I kloni je se.
If I got to come back here, things are gonna get bloody.
I ako se vratim ponovo stvari ce biti krvave.
Maybe I should just finish this now.
Mozda bi trebalo da zavrsim ovo sada.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hej, hej, hej, hej, hej.
We have to find Charlene.
Moramo da nadjemo Charlene.
I thought you hated Charlene.
Mislila sam da mrzis Charlene.
I found out she's innocent.
Saznao sam da je nevina.
I knew it. I knew it.
Znao sam. Znao sam.
Where am I gonna find her?
Gde da je nadjem sada?
Well, you can call her.
Dobro, mozes da je nazoves.
How can I call her if I don't know where she is?
Kako mogu da je nazovem kada neznam gde je?
I gave her your phone, in case you might...
Dala sam joj tvoj telefon, u slucaju da...
You gave her my new $600 titanium cellphone?
dala si joj moj novi $ 600 titanijumski mobilni?
Good idea. Come on.
Dobra ideja. Hajde.
W-What happened to your head?
S-sta ti se desilo sa glavom?
Metropolitan Museum of Art. How may I help you?
Metropoiitan muzej umetnosti. Kako vam mogu pomoci?
I know who set you up.
Znam ko ti je smestio.
What?! Who?
Sta? Ko?
Get in.
Ulazi.
So, what's up?
Dakle, sta se desilo?
The guy points a gun to my head
Tip koji mi je uperio pistolj u glavu
and tells me not to reopen the case.
rekao mi je da ne otvaram ponovo slucaj.
I'm thinking, "Why is he doing this?"
I razmisljam, zasto to radi?
And then it dawns on me... it's because he was involved.
I onda mi sine... To je zato sto je umesan.
God damn him.
Prokletstvo.
I can't believe Widow did this to me.
Nemogu da verujem da mi je Widow namestio.
Where do you think he is?
Gde mislis da je?
I don't know.
Nemam pojma.
Probably downtown at this club he hang out at
Verovatno "down town" u njegovom klubu
Got to get a confession.
Moram da odem tamo.
You can't go there.
Nemozes da ides tamo.
Eh, man, I'm serious.
Ej, covece, ozbiljan sam.
A white man at the Down Low
Beli covek tamo dole.
is either a cop, a corpse, or a crackhead.
Vec vidim lomljenje raznih delova tela.
You can't even talk 'hood.
Ti neznas ni da pricas kao iz kraja.
I'll figure out something.
Smislicu vec nesto.
Oh, and Howie told me to tell you
O, i Howie mi je rekao da ti kazem
that "The cool points are out the window,
ovo da je poenta da izadjes na prozor,
and you got him all twisted up in the game."
i zavrtis se u igri...
Really?
Stvarno?
That's the nicest thing anybody's ever said to me.
To je nesto najlepse sto sam ikada cula.
I'm gonna drop you off here
Ostavicu te ovde
because I got to get to the office for a conference call.
zato sto moram na posao zbog conferencije.
So, I'll see you in a little bit.
Vidimo se malo kasnije.
All right. Okay, cool.
Uredu. Vazi, opusteno.
Yeah, freak boy, I need a ride.
Hej, nakazo, treba mi prevoz.
Can you come now?
Mozes li da dodjes sada?
Damn. A straight, cold pimp.
Prokletsvo.
I can assure you, Mrs. Arness,
Mogu vas ubediti, gdjo Arness,
Peter Sanderson is no longer affiliated
Peter Sanderson nije vise kod nas.
with Tobias, Kline, and Barnes.
Sa Tobias, Kiine, I Barnes-om.
Good.
Odlicno.
You have great ankles.
Imate divne zglobove.
What?!
Sta?!
Were you a dancer?
Vi ste plesacica?
Yeah... well, yes. I was.
Daa... ma, da. Bila sam.
I bet you had great presence.
Kladim se da imate dobro drzanje.
Oh. How you two doin'?
Oo. Kako vam ide?
I hope I'm not interruptin' anything.
Nadam se da ne prekidam nista.
You're nasty.
Ti si pokvaren.
W-What are you doing here?
S-sta vi radite ovde?
Please, Mrs. Arness, I'm not here to cause any trouble.
Molim vas, gdjo Arness, nisam ovde da bih pravila probleme.
Well, that would be a first.
Dobro, to bi bilo prvo.
Julia? Julia?
Juiia? Juiia?
Julia a little tied up right now.
Juiia malo umorna sada.
I just need you to hear me out.
Samo mi je potrebno da me saslusate na minut.
Peter is not responsible for any of this. I am.
Peter nije odgovoran nizasta. Ja sam.
I mean, the guy is a great lawyer.
Mislim, lik je odlican advokat.
And he's one of the most decent men I've ever known.
I jedan od najljubaznih ljudi koje poznajem.
- I doubt that's saying much. - Shut up, fool.
- Nebih bas rekao. - Umukni, budalo.
If only you knew the lengths he's willing to go to
Samo da znate dokle je on spreman da ide
to help a friend.
da bi pomogao prijatelju.
Listen... sister...
Slusaj... sestro...
"Sister"?
"sestro"?
Why don't you go back to Sanderson,
Zasto se lepo nevratis onda Senderson-u,
and the "Jungle Fever" thing the two of you got goin' on,
i "groznici dzungle" gde vas dvoje treba da idete,
before I call the cops?
pre nego sto pozovem policiju?
That's it, pretty boy.
E sad je dosta, lepotane.
You ever met the big hurt?
Jesi li ikada sreo veliku ozledu?
The who?
Koga?
I wouldn't do that if I were you!
Nebih to uradila na vasem mestu!
And why not?
A zasto ne?
You'll be instantly returned to prison, where you belong.
Bicete ubrzo vraceni u zatvor, gde vam je i mesto.
All right. That's it.
Uredu. Sad je stvarno dosta.
How dare you!
Kako se usudjujete!
To hell with what I just said.
Dodjavola sa tim sto sam sada rekla.
You obviously one of them hard learners.
Ti si ocigledno jedna od onih koji tesko uce.
Howie?
Howie?
This is my house! I will not be told to do what I...
Ovo je moja kuca! I nece mi se naredjivati...
William.
Wiiiiam.
I'm Kate Sanderson. Have you seen my kids?
Ja sam Kate Sanderson. Jeste li videli moju decu?
- Over there. - Oh!
- Eno tamo. - Oo!
Hey!
Hej!
Oh, God!
Oo, Boze!
What is going on?
Sta se desava?
It's just the FBI, Mom.
Ma to je samo FBI, mama.
Yeah, they're just doing a, like, search.
Daa, oni samo nesto, valjda traze.
For what?
Zbog cega?
Well, for Charlene. But she's not...
Pa, zbog Charlene. Ali ona nije...
The FBI is looking for your nanny?
FBI trazi vasu dadilju?
Man, take your hands off me!
Covece, skloni ruke sa mene!
I said, back off me, punk!
Rekao sam, odjebi, majmune!
Excuse me...
Lzvinite...
Homeboys...
ortaci...
Say, yo. You got a bathroom in there?
Hej, y o. Imas li WC unutra?
Say, yo, what's the dealio?
Hej, y o, sta se daje?
Mmm. Who's your daddy?
Mmm. Ko je tvoj otac?
Back that booty up and put it on the glass.
Vrati tu dobit i vrati je u casu.
Anybody here dig what I'm sayin'?
Da li je neko cuo sta sam rekao?
So...
Dakle...
your nanny was doing time...
Vasa dadilja je...
for armed robbery.
izvrsila oruzanu pljacku.
And then she broke out of prison...
I onda je pobegla iz zatvora...
...and then she came here.
...i onda je dosla ovde.
But she's innocent...
Ali je nevina...
and now your dad has gone off to...
i sada ce vas otac da joj...
help her.
pomogne.
Sounds crazy, right?
Zvuci ludo, jel tako?
He's not the same guy anymore.
On vise nije isti covek.
Yeah, he's really cool.
Daa, bas je cool.
Say, any of you homies holdin' extra Jimmy High?
Hej, da li neko od vas ortaka drzi ekstra Jimmy High?
'Cause I'm all about crunchin' some of that boofanny tonight.
Zato sto hocu malo da vam pokazem taj boof veceras.
If you harm one hair on that dog's head...
Ako bude falila dlaka tom psu... If y o u h a rm o n e h a i r o n t h a t d og ' s h ea d...
Yeah, "Harm a hair on the head." You got me all nervous.
Daa, ostetiti dlaku s'glave. Bas ste me unervozili.
Hello?
Halo?
- Sarah? - Oh, hey, Charlene.
Sarah? - Oo, hej, Charlene.
Put your daddy on the phone.
Daj mi tvog tatu na telefon.
No, he's not here. He went out to find you.
Ne, pa on nije ovde. Otisao je da te nadje.
He went to find me?!
Otisao mene da nadje?!
Tsk. All right.
Tsk. Uredu.
Howie, flip a "U." We headed downtown.
Howie, pali u down town.
Downtown's where I live, precious.
Down town ' s tamo zivim, prelepa.
No! No!
- Ne! Ne!
Whoa!
Whoa!
What's on your mind, player?
Sta ti je na palo na um, igracu?
What's with you? You been drinkin' some "Hatorade"?
Sta ti je? Pio si neki "Hatorade"? Ne!
What's up, Flavor? Where you from?
Sta ima, zacinu? Odakle si?
From the 'hood and misunderstood.
Lz kraja, mis izes mi jaja.
- How's your pimp hand, dog? - Strong, baby, strong.
- Kako ti je pimp-ruka, keru? - Jaka, veoma jaka.
Can you swerve, snowman?
Moze li da napravis zaokret, snesko?
Do I got "honky" spray-painted on my forehead?
Da li "h o n ky" da isaram sprejom po mojoj glavi?
Of course I can. I'm tryin' to peep a bowwow.
Naravno da umem. Pokusavam da virim u luku.
If you so at home, man, then dance with the woman.
Ako si kao kod kuce, covece, onda igraj sa zenskom.
I can't. I got b'ness.
Nemogu. Imam p'sla
Go on out there and get your groove on.
Idi tamo i pokazi svoj groove.
No, I can't. I got important b'ness to take care of.
Ne, nemogu. Imam jedan veoma vazan p'sao da sredim.
Yeah.
Daa.
I tell you, but...
Recicu ti, ali...
You'll get a life sentence for this.
Dobicete dozivotnu za ovo.
You're a kidnapper and a whore!
Vi ste kidnaper i prostitutka!
Hey. Keep talkin', tea bag.
Hej. Nastavi da citas, vreco caja.
Ooh?! Tea bag!
Oo?! Vreca caja!
Yeah, you'll be gummin' your bubbles.
Daa, zvakacete svoje mehure.
Yeah, oh! Terrible.
Daa, oo! Uzasno.
Damn, boy, you lookin' all kind of stupid.
Prokletnice, izgledas sav u glupostima.
Really?
Stvarno?
'Cause I got this outfit from your mama.
Zato sto me je montirala tvoja mama.
Yo, Eminem, cut the wigger shit.
Yo, Eminem, skrati taj ruzni govor.
I don't think you know how much trouble you in.
Nemislim da znas u kakvoj si nevolji.
Fine, fine, fine.
Lepo, lepo, lepo.
I'm here to talk business...
Ja sam ovde da bih razgovarali o poslu...
private business.
privatnom poslu.
What fresh air is this?
Koji je ovo svez vazduh?
I don't see him anywhere.
Nevidim ih?
I think he's in that back room over there.
Mislim da je tamo.
What do we do with Her Majesty?
Sta cemo sa njenim visocanstvom?
Sit down.
Sedi tamo.
What?
Sta?
Sit it on down.
Seediii tamoo.
Now, look, if you move,
Sad, slusaj, ako se pomeris,
your little Willy gonna be bridged down.
tvoj mali willy bice bacen s'mosta.
- You dig? - Dig.
- Kontas? - Kontam.
All right. Come on.
Uredu. Hajde.
Is that real?
Jel to pravo?
Oh.
Ooo.
Uh, Seven and Seven, double.
Uu, sedam i sedam, duplo.
How you doin'?
Kako ste '?
What?!
Sta?!
I said, "How you doin'?"
Rekao sam, "Kako ste '?"
Oh, fantastic.
Oo, fantasticno.
You either the dumbest cracker I ever met or you straight up...
Ili si najgluplji covek koga sam ikad sreo ili totalno straight...
Hold that thought. I love this song.
stani malo zilavi. Volim ovu stvar.
Turn that off.
Ugasi to.
Get everybody up out of here.
Izadjite svi odavde.
I'm telling you, he is definitely in there.
Kazem ti on je definitivno tamo.
Okay, all right, so he's in there,
Dobro, on je unutra,
and then you go in, and then what happens?
i ti ulazis unutra i sta se desava onda?
Three seconds.
Tri sekunde.
Why you here?
Zasto si ovde?
I got a feeling you're sitting on a hefty sum of stolen cash.
Lmam osecaj da jos uvek sedis na gomili neopranog novca.
You want to hide it, you need a lawyer.
Hoces da ga sakrijes, potreban ti je advokat.
What's with the phone?
Sta je sa telefonom?
I'm calling in the cavalry.
Zovem, konjicu.
You'll go back to prison.
Otici ces u zatvor.
So you wanna help me launder my money?
Znaci, hoces da mi pomognes da mi operes novac?
I can hide it in an untraceable account
Mogu da ga sakrijem na skriveni racun
in the Cayman Islands.
na Cayman ostrva.
All I want is $ 100,000.
Sve sto hocu je $ 100, 000.
We both walk out of here wealthier men.
I obojca izlazimo odavde kao bogati i casni ljudi.
And I tell you where Charlene is... that simple.
I reci cu vam gde je Charlene... to je prosto.
You wearin' a wire?
Jesi li ozvucen?
Me?
Ja?
No. Are you?
Ne. A ti?
Then... then they kidnapped me.
Onda... su me oni kidnapovali.
And they took my dog, William.
I uzeli mi psa, wiiiiam-a.
That's a damn shame.
To je prokleto sramno.
Oh, you don't care.
Oo, vama nije stalo.
You smokin', Grandma?
Pusis li bakice?
Why not?
Sto da ne?
To hell with your proposition.
Dodjavola s'tvojim predlogom.
Hold it. Charlene is ready to roll over on you.
Stani bre. Charlene je spremna dati se vrti.
She knows who your accomplice was.
Zna koji je tvoj kompleks bio.
- Oh, that's pretty funny. - I'm not kidding.
- Oo, to je stvarno smesno. - Nesalim se.
They're out in the parking lot waiting for my signal and...
Eno je na parkingu i ceka moj signal...
and... and... and the signal is...
i... i... i signal je...
if I don't come back, they call the FBI.
Ako se nevratim, zvace FBI.
There was no accomplice, fool.
Nije bilo kompleksa, budalo.
There was a girl in the photo.
Bila je devojka na fotografiji.
No, there was somebody in a wig and a dress.
Ne, nego neko ko je prerusen u nju.
You...
Ti...
You left her clothes, the gun, and the money.
Ostavio si njenu odecu, pistolj i novac
See?
Vidis?
You just too damn smart for your own good.
Previse si pametan za tvoje dobro.
Look, we can't wait no more.
Vidi, nemozemo da cekamo vise.
Wait, wait. Charlene!
Stani, stani. Charlene!
Open up. Widow wanna see me.
Otvori. Widow hoce da me vidi.
Says who?
Ko kaze?
Says Lene.
Kaze lene.
Pete.
Peter.
Well, ain't this a psychic moment?
Vidi, zar nije ovo psihicki momenat?
I was just comin' to see you.
Dosao sam samo da te vidim.
Come on, Widow. This is between me and you.
Hajde, Widow. Ovo je izmedju mene i tebe.
Let him go.
Pusti ih.
No problem.
Nema probiema.
Ugh!
Ugh!
Oh, shit.
Ou, sranje.
What... come on, now. What are you doin'?
Sta... hajde, sad. Sta to radis?
Ugh!
Ugh!
I got it.
Lmam ga.
- Aim it, aim it, Howie! - Yeah!
Howie! - Daa!
Uh-huh! Who got the gun now, huh?
Uf - huu! Ko ima sad pistolj, haa?
Who got that gun now? Homie, that's right.
Ko ima sad pistolj? Homie, ovako valja.
Get y'all asses on the ground!
Spustite sva dupeta na pod!
Asses on the ground where I can see 'em, huh?
Dupeta na pod gde mogu da ih vidim, haa?
Take him out!
Vodi ih napolje!
Pussies.
Pickice.
Wasn't that fun?
Nije li toliko smesno?
I'm just gonna roll up on out of here.
Ja idem sada rolam dupe odavde.
Thank you.
Hvala ti.
- Aah! - FBI!
- Aah! - FBI!
Everybody, freeze!
Svi, ruke u vis!
Charlene! Charlene! Oh, baby!
Charlene! Charlene! Oo, duso!
Oh, oh, baby.
Oo, oo, duso!
Charlene.
Charlene.
Son of a...
Majcin sin...
Drop it!
Baci!
Oh, Charlene.
Oo, Charlene.
What?
Sta?
Damn, dog.
Prokletstvo, keru.
Hey, Howie, she's all right.
Hej, Howie, ona je dobro.
Charlene...
Charlene...
I...
Ja...
Do me a favor, precious.
Ucini mi uslugu, omiljena.
Don't ever scare me like that again,
Nemoj vise nikada da me tako uplasis,
or I'm gonna have to give you a nasty spanking,
lli cu morati da ti dam jedan prljavi kraljevski kratki...
if I'm not being too subtle.
Ako nisam dovoljno subtilan.
He's such a damn freak.
On je takva prokleta nakaza.
Are you Sanderson?
Jesi li ti Sanderson?
Yeah.
Daa.
Wait, wait. She's innocent.
Stanite, stanite. Ona je nevina.
Save it.
Snimi to.
I can prove it.
Mogu da dokazem
Mr. Sanderson... that was pretty ballsy.
g. Sanderson... bilo je previse hrabro.
You'd make a hell of an agent.
Vi ste vraski agent.
Oh, thank you very much, but I don't think I did anything
O, hvala vam mnogo, ali mislim da nisam bas sve uradio...
- an ordinary man wouldn't do... - Thanks again.
- kao jedan obican covek koji... - Hvala jos jednom.
Mr. Sanderson...
G. Sanderson...
There you are.
tu ste.
You have behaved abonidably.
Vi ste se poneli odvratn.
Aboni...
Odvrat...
Abomidably.
Odmratno.
- Abodi... - Abominably.
- Odmrat... - Odvratno.
I know.
Znam.
- Shakespeare.
- Shakespeare. - Shakespeare.
No, wait. This is serious.
Ne, cekaj. Ovo je ozbiljno.
Oh, to hell with it.
Oo, dovraga s'tim.
I do believe I'm stoned.
Verujem da sam stondirana.
Just don't tell anybody you ever saw me like this.
Samo nemojte reci nikome da ste me videli ovakvu.
Mrs. Arness...
Gdjo. Arness...
William.
wiiiiam.
Oh, God, you are an ugly dog...
Oo, Boze, ti si jedan srecan pas...
and heavy.
i tezak.
Here, I got him.
Evo, uhvatio sam ga.
Thank you.
Hvala vam.
Is there a 24-hour diner around here?
Ima li ovde neka klopa ublizini?
I know where one is. I'll take you there.
Znam za jednu. Odvescu vas tamo.
I'm dreadfully hungry.
Strasno sam gladna.
You guys okay?
Vi ste uredu?
What do you think?
Sta ti mislis?
Yo, be cool, G-mo.
Yo, opusteno.
Yo, out back, G-mo.
Yo, opusteno nazad.
Full cheesy, homey.
Fuiicheesy, ortak.
Well, that's not good enough.
Onda, to nije dovoljno dobro.
You'll just have to keep trying, won't you?
Moras da nastavis sa trudom, zar ne?
I called Arness four times. She'll only talk to Peter.
Zvao sam gdju Arness cetiri puta. Ona hoce da razgovara samo Peter-om.
Well, we're just gonna have to keep him around.
Dobro, znaci onda moramo da ga zadrzimo da bude tu.
Oh, hey, guys.
Ou, hej, momci.
Peter.
Peter.
Did I mention I'm going out on my own?
Da li sam vam pomenuo da odlazim svojevoljno?
You don't have the resources.
Ti nemas izvore.
Well, I have one multibillion-dollar client.
Dobro, imam jedan multimilijarderskog-klijenta.
It's a start.
To je za pocetak.
And a partner.
I partnera.
I'm all over it, G.
Ja sam skroz tu, g.
Let's go.
Idemo.
Excuse me.
Izvinite me.
Peter, we can talk about this.
Peter, mozemo da razgovaramo o tome.
Ed, you can kiss my natural black ass.
Ed, mozes da me poljubis u moje prirodno crno dupe.
Peter...
Peter...
Ashley, who are you doing here?
Ashiey, Koga ti radis ovde?
Oh, I was, uh, meeting, uh, uh...
Oo, Ja sam, uu, sastanak, uu, uu...
- for my aunt's estate. - About her aunt's estate.
Za moj zajam. - Za njen zajam.
There was a codicil.
Konsultacije.
Well, say goodbye to half your stuff.
Dobro, oprosti se od pola svojih stvari.
I'll call you.
Zvacu te.
Lookin' good, kids. Almost there.
Pogledajte dobro klinci. Skoro smo ovde.
Peter, your 4:00 is waiting for you in your office.
Peter, ceka vas stranka u vasoj kancelariji.
I don't have any meetings today.
Nemam nikakav sastanak danas.
I'm sorry. I didn't realize I had an appointment.
Zao mi je ali nisam znao da ima sastanak.
Hey.
Hej.
So, this is how a big-time tax attorney lives, huh?
Dakle, ovako izgledazivot velikog advokata za takse, haa?
This place is big pimpin', P. Diddy.
Ovo mesto je zaista veliko, p. Diddy.
- How you doin'? - I'm a'ight.
- Kako si? - Dobro sam.
I really wanted to tell you again
Stvarno zelim da ti kazem ponovo
how much I appreciate what you did for me.
koliko cenim to sto si uradio za mene.
If I could only give you back half of what you've given me.
Da mogu da ti vratim samo pola od onoga sto si ti meni ucinila.
Please. We'll call it even. Now give me a hug.
Molim te. Mi to zovemo jednako. Hajde daj mi jedan zagrljaj.
Hey, white people don't hug.
Hej, beli ljudi se ne grle.
You ain't white.
Pa ti nisi beo.
Well, I'm off-white.
Dobro, iskljucio sam belo.
Good to see you.
Dobro je videti te.
Kate...
Kate...
Hi.
Zdravo.
Um, oh, well, I'm, uh...
Um, oo, dobro, Ja, uu...
I got to finish up some things with Howie.
Imam da zavrsim neke stvari sa Howie-em.
Oh, Kate, this is Charlene. Charlene, this is Kate.
Oo, Kate ovo je Charlene. Charlene ovo je Kate.
Hi. You've certainly been shaking things up around here.
Zdravo. Vi sigurno vec vrckate stvari ovuda.
Well, shakin' is what I do best.
Pa, vrckanje je ono sto najbolje radim.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Kate.
Drago mi je da smo se upoznale, Kate.
Thank you.
Hvala ti.
And take care of him for me.
I pobrini mi se za njega.
Hi.
Zdravo.
So...
Dakle...
what... what brings you down?
Sta... sta te dovodi ovamo?
I mean, you know, not what brings you down,
Mislim, znas, ne sta te dovodi ovamo,
but, I mean, what brings you down here?
nego, mislim sta de dovodi ovde kod mene?
Well, I was just wondering, um...
Pa, pitala sam se, umm...
how often do you take that shortcut past my house?
koliko si cesto isao tom precicom pored moje kuce?
Technically?
Tehnicki?
Uh, well...
Uu, pa...
uh, pretty much every day.
uu, veoma cesto svaki dan...
Well, you know, technically...
Pa, znas, tehnicki...
That's stalking.
sunjao si se.
It's kind of cute.
To je nekako slatko.
Kate...
Kate...
There's something I want to say to you.
Nesto hocu da ti kazem.
The cool points are out the window,
Poenta je izaci na prozor,
and I'm all twisted up in the game.
i malo uvrcemo se u igri.
What does that mean?
Sta to znaci?
It means I love you.
To znaci da te volim.
What you think?
Sta mislis?
Holler at your boy.
Hower kakav si deckic.
- Hey. - Nothin' is nothin'.
- Hej. - nista je nista '.
Who's your daddy now?
Ko je tvoj tata sad?
Boy, you are some kind of freaky.
Decko, ti si neka vrsta nakaze.